Chapter 184: Rank five intense battle

"Tie Xue Leng, why is he suddenly here?" Fang Yuan recognised the voice, feeling shocked.

This loud voice echoed above the blood pond, causing intense waves to form.

"This is... Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu?" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth. As the loud voice hurt his eardrums, he felt his entire brain buzzing.

Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu, a Rank five Gu, was from a sound-type Gu. Once activated, it could form soundwave attacks that had a wide range, belonging to an extremely strong area-of-effect attacking-type Gu.

The voice that Fang Yuan was hearing now, is only Tie Xue Leng's probing; it was just him slightly shouting and not activating his Gu completely.

This intensity was like Fang Yuan using the Moonlight Gu to open the purple gold rock; it was a type of in-depth control of his Gu worm.

Of course, the Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu also had its weakness. If used for long, it would cause great strain to the Gu Master's throat and vocal cord. Once his limit is exceeded, the Gu Master would become completely mute, losing his ability to speak.

Bam!

A loud explosion occurred as blood and water flew everywhere.

The top half of the huge python's body appeared in Fang Yuan's vision.

Blood river python!

Fang Yuan's irises shrunk as he saw the python with its bright smooth blood red scales, and its head around the size of an elephant. Scarlet-gold coloured sharp bone spikes protruded out from above its eyes, showing its ferocious and frenzy aura completely.

"Blood river python... I remember that in the Gu Yue clan's history, after the first generation clan leader created the village, a blood river python appeared and was a huge threat to the village. Legend says the first gen killed it, but don't tell me..."

Fang Yuan's thoughts moved, thinking of something.

The blood river python was humongous, snake head high in the air, its purple irises staring right at Fang Yuan with two ruthless glances.

It had a ruthless nature, untamable and fed on blood. Even if the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura tried to suppress it, that would only cause it to become more frenzied. Among Rank five Gu worms, it was one of the hardest to refine.

But after the blood river python took a look at Fang Yuan up on the walls, it raised its head higher and turned towards the top of the cave.

At the top of the cave, there was another tiny shadow, floating down from one of the holes at the ceiling.

He wore a bronze mask, his hands behind his back, his gaze cool and calm. Although compared to the blood river python, he was small like an ant, but the imposing aura coming from his body caused a great pressure to emit from him at all directions, like a heavenly being descending down to Earth.

Righteous Gu!

A mind-type Gu that only someone who upheld justice could activate.

People who were villainous or had weak minds and aspirations, were often scared shitless under the influence of the Righteous Gu, afraid of everything as they had a guilty conscience, their battle spirit decreasing in battle and causing them to feel an inability to defeat Tie Xue Leng, thus collapsing without battle.

Screech screech....

Under the pressure of the righteousness, the bladewing blood bat Gu were frantic and could only scream shrilly as a strong pressure pushed down on their bodies. Their wings could only continue to flap as they struggled to stay in mid-air, floating up and down.

They could barely take care of themselves, much less bother about Fang Yuan.

Even the ferocious blood river python slightly lowered its head, feeling Tie Xue Leng's supreme presence.

"What a good Righteous Gu!" Fang Yuan climbed on the wall, smirking.

This suppression from the Righteous Gu had no effect on him. Only those with weak minds could be greatly weakened. He was a supreme demonic overlord, his mind strong as steel, how could this illusionary pressure scare him?

"Eh?" Fang Yuan's immunity caused Tie Xue Leng to call out in shock, feeling very surprised.

The Righteous Gu had been with him for many years, and he was very sure about the Gu's effect.

Righteous Gu's effect varied. It attacked the mind directly, sometimes having great effect while other times having no effect.

But the times where it did not work, were almost nonexistent. Even righteous people felt a strong suppression in their hearts. After all, their factions did not determine a person's kindness and evil; there are no perfect humans.

But Tie Xue Leng knew deeply about Fang Yuan's crimes. The first time they met, he already implanted a Gu on Fang Yuan, using it to track his whereabouts. After that, Tie Xue Leng could faintly discern the changes in the surroundings where Fang Yuan went.

Those who committed great sins, under the Righteous Gu, would definitely waver. But Tie Xue Leng also met a good number of demonic Gu Masters, that were unaffected by the righteous aura.

"There is only one type of person who would be unaffected by the Righteous Gu even after commiting sins. These are the people with real demonic nature, in the deepest parts of their hearts. They are crazy and adamant, not treating their sins as sins, but thinking of it as natural. To think that this Fang Yuan has such an intense demonic nature! Hmph, I'll get rid of this great demon here first. If Fang Yuan manages to survive, I will come and finish him later!"

Tie Xue Leng hated evil with a burning passion. With a cold snort, he turned towards the blood river python.

Once he appeared, he was locked on by this blood river python. As long as he was distracted in killing Fang Yuan, he would reveal a weakness.

Tie Xue Leng had such a severe injury on him, and at the same time there might be a powerful enemy hidden in the background and observing him. Thus, he did not dare to lose focus.

He stared at this blood river python for a moment, before looking further into the blood pond.

Not long ago, he received a mysterious letter. Inside there was concrete evidence that Gu Yue village held a bloody calamity.

This letter was held by a red-crowned crane coming from the sky, with a questionable source.

But Tie Xue Leng would rather believe it than miss it. After all, the blood calamity was not ordinary, he could not take it lightly. If he lost focus, it would expand and spread like a plague, harming the world.

The best method to deal with it was to eliminate the source before it forms into a strong force.

Coincidentally, he already had another request at hand—it was Jia Fu paying a high cost to ask him to investigate Jia Jin Sheng's death.

Tie Xue Leng thus brought his daughter and rushed to Qing Mao Mountain.

He ordered his daughter to investigate Jia Jin Sheng's case. It was to nurture and train Tie Ruo Nan, but also to act as a red herring, stalling for time and hiding in the background investigating this issue.

The first time when he met Fang Yuan, he implanted a Shared-sense Gu on him. Although it was merely at a whim, he did it due to his accumulated experience and instinct.

Shared-sense Gu was formless and colorless, like a signet. He had implanted over tens of them, but the only successful one was the first one he implanted.

"First gen Gu Yue, I know you are not dead. You hid for nearly a thousand years plotting this scheme, but unfortunately, it's all going down the drain." Tie Xue Leng opened his mouth, causing the air to tremble.

But there were no changes to the blood pond. Instead, the blood river python opened its mouth, screaming furiously.

It was born ferocious, unable to be suppressed. The Righteous Gu triggered its ferocity.

Bam.

It stretched its body abruptly, the huge snake body rising with the tides of blood, bringing a killing intent that tore through the skies, pouncing towards Tie Xue Leng who was in mid-air.

Tie Xue Leng was already wary against the blood river python, and he quickly moved, avoiding the blood river python's bite.

The python's body was too long, and its momentum was too strong. It ended up crashing all the way onto the ceiling of the cave.

A loud bang ensued as a portion of the ceiling collapsed, and large amounts of debris fell and caused much commotion in the blood lake waves.

"Hmph, First gen Gu Yue, you think you are safe with just a blood python protecting you? You might as well appear now," Tie Xue Leng snickered. He moved about in the air, and the blood river python's attacks were like a gentle rain pelting on him.

The blood river python attacked furiously, getting more worked up as it continued to miss.

It had unparalleled strength, able to display it all and cause great damage.

The entire space was shaking from its strength like an earthquake, and the blood lake began to raise strong ripples.

"Fuck!" Fang Yuan was caught by the crossfire, and as the red soil softened, his foothold had been ruined.

He could only use the Chainsaw Golden Centipede as well as the Thunderwings Gu to move along the walls. Meanwhile the rock debris was falling down like rain.

As he had expected, the Thunderwings Gu was really in bad shape. Fang Yuan's thunderwings were extremely weak and lethargic, unable to provide him much boost in speed.

But the strange thing was, the Thunderwings Gu was taking lesser and lesser primeval essence from Fang Yuan. During the period where Fang Yuan moved about, it started to absorb primeval essence from the surrounding air to replenish itself.At first, this situation was uncommon and happened in short intervals.

As Fang Yuan continued to dodge, he did not notice initially. But eventually, the intervals got shorter and the duration lengthened.

At the same time, the Thunderwings Gu got weaker and weaker.

"I get it, its the Blood Frenzy Gu!" Fang Yuan's mind shone with inspiration.

Only when affected by the Blood Frenzy Gu will such a situation occur.

Plop!

Fang Yuan put in 100% effort, but eventually still fell into the blood lake.

The blood river python was rampaging everywhere, using its thick tail to sweep across the place, causing large debris to fall like rain.

Fang Yuan activated the Sky Canopy Gu, covering himself with a white armor. He was good at swimming. In his previous life he had lived in the Eastern Sea for a long time, thus he had sufficient training.

The falling rocks were as large as houses, and he tried his best to avoid them. Sometimes he swam underwater, sinking into the lake to use the water to reduce the impact of the rocks.

But for the smaller fragments, some were fist-sized while others were like grindstones, and he could not avoid them all.

The white light armor was firm like a monolith, but it could not handle the full impact of the rocks, causing him to feel pain when they hit his armor. At the same time, his primeval essence also decreased with each hit endured.

Thankfully, the Righteous Gu's power was surrounding the area, causing the group of bladewing blood bat Gu to fly around randomly, not finding trouble with Fang Yuan.

But Fang Yuan's expression was solemn.

The Thunderwings Gu was half crippled after being corrupted by the Blood Frenzy Gu, and without a special Gu to clean it, it would soon turn into a puddle of blood water, turning into a new pollution origin.How did it get infected by the Blood Frenzy Gu?

Fang Yuan considered the previous events, and there was only one explanation—in this blood water, there was a Blood Frenzy Gu inside.

The Thunderwings Gu continued to weaken, and started to become uncontrollable.

Thankfully he activated the white light armor in time, otherwise if the Blood Frenzy Gu got into his body and entered his aperture, most of his Gu worms would get corrupted.

But if his primeval essence was expended, or if this armor was broken, the consequences would be severe!

"I have to leave this place as soon as possible!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth, trying to find a way out from the surroundings as he swam around.

Large amounts of red soil on the mountain walls collapsed from the battle.

The cave ceiling was completely destroyed beyond recognition as well. Tie Xue Leng floated in mid-air, engaging the blood river python in combat.Rank five battles were not something Fang Yuan could interfere in.

The more a Gu Master advanced, the larger the difference in battle strength among ranks.

Maybe with a sweep of the blood river python's tail, it could break the light armor and cause the Sky Canopy Gu to be gravely injured, breaking all of Fang Yuan's bones in the process. Perhaps with a simple wave of Tie Xue Leng's hands, it could send Fang Yuan falling into an impasse.

The situation right now was like two giant elephants fighting, while Fang Yuan was a domestic cat. Although he had tiny claws, there was nothing he could do.

"Wait, a cave entrance?"

Chapter 185: Gu Yue first gen, Five great flying zombies

The tunnel entrance wasn't big and should have been buried by the red soil before. But now, as the blood lake surged up in a huge wave, the red soil in the surrounding walls were washed away, sinking down in the lake. As a result, the tunnel entrance cleared up again and became visible.

No matter what, this tunnel entrance was like a light of hope. Fang Yuan immediately turned around and started swimming towards it.

BOOM!

Another intense explosion occurred in the air. The enormous force of the explosion struck the surroundings and violently pushed Fang Yuan forward.

"Damn it!" He cursed.

Great amounts of red soil had fallen down and buried the tunnel entrance again.

Iron fist grappling Gu!

In the air, Tie Xue Leng took a deep breath and slowly extended his right hand when he felt the time was right.

There was a ripple in the air before him and a giant black iron hand appeared; it appeared slow but pressed down on the blood river python's tail within moments.

Blood river python struggled fiercely, and with its wet scales and slick body, the iron hand slipped off it and burst out with golden-red light.

Tie Xue Leng, however, had plenty of battle experiences and wasn't downcast. He slightly raised his head, puffed up his cheeks and blew strongly towards the Blood River Python.

Whoosh!Pitch black oil fell down like waterfall and formed into the shape of a dragon in the air, before plunging towards the Blood River Python.

Oil Dragon Gu!

The blood River Python was furious. It snarled and started tearing at the Oil Dragon Gu.

The black oil dragon was not in the least inferior to Blood River Python in terms of physique, but it was only a Rank four Gu and did not have a physical body; it was soon torn to shreds by Blood River Python.

Tie Xue Leng smiled, on the contrary.

Beasts were beasts, if a Gu Master had personally controlled it, they would have seen through this classic and ordinary battle tactic. The Blood River Python had been refined and although it had a Gu Master's imprint on it, it didn't have the wisdom of humans.

The oil dragon was exterminated, causing backlash to the Oil Dragon Gu in the aperture.

Tie Xue Leng didn't care; he stopped using the Oil Dragon Gu then began activating Fire Dragon Gu.

He gave a loud shout and his body shook, and then a Gu that looked like a flame shot out of his aperture. The flame quickly formed into a fire snake, winding around its own body.

As the fire snake flew, it grew bigger, then it immediately started growing scales, claws, horns and sharp teeth. Its face started becoming more like that of a horse; it had changed into an enormous fire dragon.This Fire Dragon Gu was also a Rank four Gu, but it was able to cause a lot of pain to Blood River Python.This was because of the oil dragon; when it was wiped out, great amounts of black oil stuck to Blood River Python's body, and now the fire dragon was causing the oil to catch fire and roast the Blood River Python.

Besides the snake, the black oil had also fallen on the lake surface. Right now, a raging inferno was burning on the bright red blood lake, causing the air temperature to increase rapidly.

The fire dragon was not the Blood River Python's match at all, it suffered heavy injuries and kept on shrinking. But every time this happened, it would drill into the raging inferno and recover some of its power.

With the raging inferno, the fire dragon had a homeground advantage.

Blood River Python was constantly being burned as it fought with the fire dragon, there was even a smell of scorched meat coming off it.

Blood River Python had a berserk nature and it would erupt with even stronger counterattack if it got suppressed. But right now, it was actually shrinking back, giving up on the fire dragon and diving deep into the blood lake.Humans were the highest of all living beings and possessed the intelligence to develop new concepts. With Tie Xue Leng's tactics, two Rank four Gu were able to make the Rank five Blood River Python retreat.But Gu were the essence of the world, containing the secrets of heaven and earth, a portion of the natural laws. And Blood River Python's ability was extreme self recovery.

As it sank to the bottom of the lake, the blood water continuously nourished it, rapidly healing the wounds on its body. The fire dragon had the field advantage; so did the blood python. As long as the blood lake existed, it was like a cockroach that couldn't be killed.

Fang Yuan's situation was even more perilous.

The inferno on the surface of the blood lake was constantly spreading, burning even hotter, and the flames were roasting him alive.

The pressure on the Sky Canopy Gu was getting bigger and bigger. But the most critical point was not this, but rather it was the increasing difficulty in breathing.

The flames used great amounts of air to maintain their combustion, and this place is underground and was originally a half-sealed area, which meant it took more time to replenish the used oxygen. Fang Yuan was gradually starting to feel suffocated.

"Although Oil Dragon Gu and Fire Dragon Gu sent Blood River Python retreating with their combined efforts, this is only temporary. As long as there are large amounts of blood water, Blood River Python will recover with a terrifying rate. Once it comes out, it will have recovered to its peak state and the Fire Dragon Gu would no longer be its match. But, this is basic knowledge, it is impossible for Tie Xue Leng to not know this. Then he...."Fang Yuan bobbed up and down on the blazing lake; his thoughts were revolving rapidly. And his heart tensed when he thought of this.

If he wasn't wrong, Tie Xue Leng should have achieved his intention by making Blood River Python retreat.Tie Xue Leng needed enough time and he needed the situation to be like this to prepare his following killing move.

Sure enough, in the next moment, while floating in the air Tie Xue Leng suddenly extended both his arms and a deep roar emerged from his mouth.

He withdrew the righteous aura that had been suppressing everything, and whole-heartedly poured his Rank five primeval essence into the copper mask.

The copper mask started to brighten up; it was only a glimmer at first but within few breaths of time, it burst out with an extremely dazzling green light, as bright as a fragment of the sun.

The green light shone upon everything like a monarch overlooking the heavens and earth. For a moment, the red soil, blood lake and raging inferno were covered with a layer of dark green light.

The green light contained a mystical power.

Under this power, the mountain rocks began to shake and crumble.

From above the cave, huge rocks came crumbling down, flying towards the copper mask. Great amounts of soil and rocks from the top to bottom of the red walls also slowly flew up.

Tie Xue Leng's face was already shrouded by the light from the copper mask. Great amounts of mountain rocks gathered around the copper mask and condensed together into a human shape.Debris continuously converged from all around and the rock figure kept on getting bigger.

From one meter in the beginning, it rapidly grew to three meters... five meters... eight meters... and finally reached eighteen meters!

Giant Mountain Puppet Gu!

The giant figure with indomitable spirit descended towards the blood lake.

Its two feet touched the bottom of the blood lake, but the water only reached up to about its waist. Its body was very robust and grand; horse chariots could run on its two arms and it could hold an elephant on its fist.

Its face looked simple and unadorned; it was the enlarged version of the copper mask.

"Fire dragon, come." It spoke, and its voice seemed to shake the heavens and earth.

The fire dragon which was churning in the fire sea flew up and coiled around the giant puppet's right arm like a snake, and its head rested on the right shoulder of the giant puppet.

Next, the Oil Dragon Gu flew out and formed a pitch black oil dragon which coiled around the giant puppet's left arm and its head rested on the left shoulder of the giant puppet.

With dragons on his left and right, the giant figure appeared like a heavenly deity descending down!

Fang Yuan used all his strength to swim towards the tunnel entrance. When the debris had flown and formed the giant puppet, the red soil covering the tunnel entrance had also gone with it, once again revealing the opening.

This battlefield was becoming more dangerous, the tunnel entrance could be buried again at any time; Fang Yuan didn't dare to stay longer.The fire sea gradually died out, and suddenly a huge red wave rose from the blood lake.

Blood River Python initiated its attack from the lake; it coiled around the giant puppet and moved upwards. The giant snake head smashed towards the giant puppet's face like a ram.

This attack was very powerful and if it really struck, more than half of the giant puppet's head would be destroyed."Iron fist grappling!" The giant puppet shouted; the air split open and an iron hand flew out, grabbing at the snake head.

With a loud boom, the iron hand shattered but Blood River Python's attack was also stopped.

Tie Xue Leng won a brief respite. The giant puppet's two hands grabbed towards Blood River Python in tandem.Oil dragon and fire dragon seized the chance and climbed Blood River Python. The two snake combined and formed a blazing flame, roasting Blood River Python.

Blood River Python kept on hissing in pain and struggled furiously. But why would Tie Xue Leng let it escape so easily? The giant puppet's hands were like pincers as they firmly pressed on the Blood River Python.

The Blood River Python was not able to escape. Its body was scorched black, giving off the smell of burnt meat. This stimulated its vicious nature; since it couldn't escape, it coiled around the giant puppet and violently contracted, trying to kill it by constriction.

Although the giant puppet was made from condensed mountain rocks, its body had the softness of the red soil. With Blood River Python's constricting force, its waist quickly shrunk by a fold.

Cracking sounds emerged, and fragments of rocks flew in all directions.

Under the stimulation of death, Blood River Python burst forth with an even greater strength.

Fang Yuan finally climbed to the edge of the tunnel entrance, when suddenly the giant puppet gave out coughing sounds.Tie Xue Leng's old illness had reappeared!

The giant puppet's hands loosened, and the Blood River Python hissed and its body suddenly jumped ahead.

However, the giant puppet's hands tightened again. The Blood River Python opened its mouth wide and revealed its sharp fangs, its head crazily swaying but it still fell short by a distance.

It was not able to retaliate and it was gradually losing its strength; it would burn to death soon.

But right at this moment, dense bloody fog rose up from the middle of the blood lake.

"Blood Frenzy Gu!" Fang Yuan's eyes showed a hint of dread; he immediately climbed the tunnel entrance and went inside it.

The bloody fog rapidly pervaded the air, and the raging inferno on the bloodlake had completely extinguished.

A whirlpool appeared in the middle of the blood lake.

The whirlpool had started from the middle of the lake and quickly spread from there, growing bigger until its edges were touching the surrounding walls.

"Humph, Gu Yue first head, you couldn't endure it anymore?...." The giant puppet coldly snorted.

A giant blood wave reaching as high as ten meters gushed out of the middle of the whirlpool.

And from within the blood wave, a vertical crimson coffin gradually rose up.

"Hehehehe...." A hoarse and strange voice was transmitted from inside the coffin, and anyone that heard this voice would feel cold to the bone.

"Young junior, thou dare spoil my plan, thou court death and I shall give it to thee!" Before the voice had died away, the coffin lid shot out like a catapult, revealing a shrivelled corpse.

He had a scarlet face and fangs, his hair red like blood, his eyes deep and contained a fire that seemed about to extinguish.

He had no skin, and thin strips of red muscles were clinging onto the white bones, giving him a shrivelled and fierce look.

"Junior, thou art wounded but yet dare to provoke me. Today, thou shalt die!!" The corpse spoke, but there was no movement in its mouth, the voice had come from its abdomen.He kept on saying 'I', 'thou'— these were the speech habits of thousand years ago.

"Rank five Blood Wight Gu! Is he really the first head?" Fang Yuan was flabbergasted, but wasn't surprised.

In this magical world, there were plenty of Gu Masters who lived for centuries. Besides using the most orthodox way of increasing lifespan through the Lifespan Gu, there were also some demonic ways to make one live forever.

For instance, the Rank two Roaming Zombie Gu.

If this Gu was used for too long, the Gu Master would turn completely into a zombie and as long as they sucked blood at specific times, they could live freely forever.

The Gu Yue first head in front of him had used such a way.

Blood Wight Gu was a major Rank five advancement route of the Roaming Zombie Gu. Along with the Asura zombie, heavenly demon zombie, nightmare zombie and plague zombie, they were called five great flying zombies.

The Lifespan Gu was difficult to find. The first head had turned himself into a blood wight flying zombie and buried himself here!

Chapter 186: Spring and autumn does not appear

In the blood lake, two strong foes opposed each other.

"Even the Rank five Blood Wight is only a zombie at the end. First gen Gu Yue, you are no longer a living person, you are full of death essence. Your aperture is dead too, and even though you can store primeval essence, every bit you use cannot be replenished, you cannot recover on your own," the giant puppet said coldly.

"Hehehe... although I cannot recover primeval essence, so what? I can continue to use primeval stones to regain primeval essence. You have an injury on you, yet you dare disturb me... die!" First gen Gu Yue shouted.

At once, blood mist spewed out, and as blood waves raged on, a large group of insects flew out from the blood lake.

It was the Rank five Blood Guillotine!

At the same time, troops of bladewing blood bats flew out from the cave ceiling and emerged from the blood lake, joining together and attacking towards the giant puppet.

A large pack of bats, almost a thousand of them, formed into a huge army.

Although they were Rank three and were a close-combat type Gu, but numbers made up for quality, even the Rank five Tie Xue Leng felt a headache fighting against them.

But that was not the end, for after First gen Gu Yue's consciousness awakened, under his command, troops of blood bats continued to show up, gathering here.

He had operated there for almost a thousand years, and had a heaven shattering scheme. He had converted the place into his personal backyard, thus having a great location advantage.

Blood bat groups were organised, staying in formation in the air, continuing to move around like a strong army, surrounding the giant puppet.

The blood river python stopped struggling, instead coiling up its body. This caused Tie Xue Leng to feel a threat, and he concentrated his mind even further.

A Gu's power although strong, was unintelligent. A blood bat army with or without a Gu Master's control, had a hell of a difference.

"First gen Gu Yue only just appeared, and yet he has turned the tables, almost suppressing Tie Xue Leng. He has great location advantage, having his troops at his disposal, while Tie Xue Leng has an injury on him, the situation is not looking good."

Fang Yuan had hid into a cave in the walls, using the shadows to hide and observe the battle.

"But Tie Xue Leng has roamed the Southern Borders for many years. With an injury on him but still entering this trap, he has to have some trump card. No matter what, there's going to be an intense battle soon, this entire district might even collapse. Should I stay here and observe? Staying here is very dangerous, this is the deepest part of the underground cave, I might get buried alive. If I stay and watch the show, what are the chances of me benefiting from their conflict?"

Fang Yuan thought quickly, evaluating the gains and losses.

He was only Rank three initial stage now, and there was a high risk in staying. As long as he got hit indirectly by one of their attacks, he would get heavily injured.

But if he really gained something from this, surviving to the end, the benefits would be overwhelming. After all, what a Rank five Gu Master owns could help him save up to a hundred years of hard work!

"High risk high return..." Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh, and planned to retreat.

The situation was no longer under his control; there was too much risk in staying.

Birds die for food, people die for fortune, these situations, he had seen much of them in his previous five hundred years of living.

He was vigilant in nature. As long as he lived, there would always be more opportunities in the future. After all, he knew countless secrets and many unexposed inheritance grounds; they were all profitable and useful to him, he did not have to risk his life here.

Just when Fang Yuan was about to leave, a small amount of blood bats flew out from the army and towards him.

This blood bat group had around a hundred, causing Fang Yuan to quickly retreat.

"My clan junior, don't worry. There are traps set up in that cave, and even underground beasts reside there. These blood bats can ensure your safety," the first gen Gu Yue's voice resounded.

When Fang Yuan heard this, he ran even faster.First gen Gu Yue was slightly shocked, not expecting Fang Yuan to be so observant at such a young age, able to sense his evil intents. Immediately, he pushed his will and another group of hundreds of blood bats chased after Fang Yuan.

His distraction caused Tie Xue Leng to discover a weakness that wasn't really a flaw.

Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu!

Howl!The giant puppet opened its mouth, giving off a howl that shook the nine heavens. At once, the overwhelming soundwaves rushed towards all directions like the sound of thunder.

The bladewing blood bat Gu closeby were instantly murdered by this power, falling down one by one.

Blood bat groups further away were in disarray from the attack, flying randomly in the air.

The concentrated bat army earlier had in a split second, gone into chaos and could not have any utility in the next short period.

Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu was as high as Rank five, and it was an area-of-effect type that specialized in dealing with blood bat groups. When Tie Xue Leng first used it, the power was not strong, but that was due to him keeping it down forcefully. Now that he used the body of the giant puppet, he could display the true power of the Heaven Earth Magnificent Sound Gu.

Even numerous Blood Guillotine all over the sky were killed. As the blood mist dispersed, clear vision returned.

The soundwaves bounced off the walls as the entire space within the mountain started trembling.

With the giant puppet as the focal point, the blood lake's water level was forced downwards, forming a bowl shape in the lake, and the blood water oozed out through the cave opening.

But before that, there were sound waves spreading.

Fang Yuan was caught in the crossfire, his white armor shimmering, almost breaking apart. To endure this soundwave attack, his aperture's primeval essence was used up by about 10%.

The soundwaves echoed in the narrow cave, and Fang Yuan's ears could not endure the buzzing and he almost tripped on the ground.

But this soundwave was at least helpful to him.

For the two groups of blood bats chasing him, the second was already decimated, and the first were in chaos from the attack, flying all over the place in the cave and not being able to chase Fang Yuan.

It was a rare chance, so Fang Yuan quickly sprinted, pulling some distance from the blood bats.This group of bats were the furthest from the soundwaves, thus recovering quickly. They flapped their wings, continuing their assault.

There were about a hundred blood bats, all Rank three. Fang Yuan could not fight against them and could only run away.

Earlier, the cave was dark and he did not know the directions. But now, his eyes had adapted to the dark environment, and he could see a bit of the area.

This was all thanks to the red soil emitting light.

Although his thunderwings were already unreliable, it could at least help a little, thus Fang Yuan activated it with all his strength.

But even so, the two had a great difference in speed, and the distance was slowly shortened.

"The distance is almost there, it's time to use the Spring Autumn Cicada!" Fang Yuan gritted his teeth. As the blood bat group continued to get closer, he could only use this method!

Bladewing blood bat Gu was only Rank three, so the Rank six Gu aura completely dominated them. But Tie Xue Leng and First gen Gu Yue were nearby.

Once the Spring Autumn Cicada appears, it would cause a great mirage and the commotion would attract their attention.

But Fang Yuan had no choice. With the situation before him, he could only hope that they were concentrated in fighting, and could not split their attention towards him.

Screech screech...

The blood bat group continued to get closer, almost less than a hundred steps away.

Fang Yuan breathed out in anticipation, thinking in his heart, "Spring Autumn Cicada, come out!"

One second, two seconds, three seconds...

Fang Yuan was stunned, standing on the spot; the Spring Autumn Cicada was in the center of his aperture, unmoving while emitting a brilliant yellow green light.

"How can this be?!" Fang Yuan was shocked.

...

Far away, the sky glowed amidst the mist.

It was dawn.

On the slope, Gu Yue Bo, Bai clan and Xiong clan leader stood side by side.

"Even though the real competition is tomorrow, we have to have a preliminary competition. The time is just right, shall we start?" Xiong clan leader smiled as he said.

Bai clan leader snorted, ignoring him.

"Then let's start." Gu Yue Bo answered while distracted. He moved his gaze to the Gu Masters gathered there, trying to search but could not find Fang Yuan among them.

His worry intensified.

These Gu Masters were all under thirty years old, and while standing together, they distinctly split into three groups.

Taking one glance, the three clan's strength was apparent.

Xiong clan had the most Gu Masters since they retreated at the start, and kept most of their battle strength. Gu Yue clan and Bai clan had less members, but Bai clan had Bai Ning Bing. He alone was enough to promote the Bai clan's overall strength to the top of the three clans.

Xiong clan leader shouted, "This competition will be held around the surrounding hundred li, all the way until night time, ending when the sun sets. Battles will not have life-and-death restrictions, but I hope you can control yourselves. You have a token in your hands, and the ones who collect thirty of them gets the qualification to enter the three-clans competition! Ready, and start!"

Life and death battles, only those who qualify can enter. There is no participation limit, and the surrounding hundred li is the stage. Even entering midway is permitted.

This is not a fair competition. But the three clan leaders did not have any opinions or grudges towards it.

In this world, survival is based on one's own strength, one's fist. The stronger you are, the more rights you have to gain more benefits. If you are weak, then you should begrudge your luck and lay low, accumulating strength and becoming strong.

...

In a few breath's time, Fang Yuan felt like two or three years had passed.

His forehead was full of cold sweat; the Spring Autumn Cicada was unable to come out, how could this happen?

Spring Autumn Cicada is his vital Gu, it was very important to him. A Rank six Gu, his final trump card, to think it could not be controlled! This was too severe, and Fang Yuan had to place all his attention on this problem.

In the dark cave, he squinted.

He only panicked for less than a second, before calming himself down.

His mind moved like lightning, his spirit entering his aperture; there was nothing wrong with the Spring Autumn Cicada, it was still recovering quickly.

But no matter how Fang Yuan willed it, it remained stagnant at the center, not moving even a single step.

"I get it!" Fang Yuan was enlightened, "This Spring Autumn Cicada, once it becomes a vital Gu, it stays in the aperture and can no longer be moved."

Gu was the essence of living beings, it had endless possibilities, and all sorts of forms and abilities.

For Gu worms—nurture, use, and refine, all three were deep and profound and often were there special cases in these aspects.

On 'nurturing', Gu worms only ate specific food. On 'refine', they had all sorts of requirements.

On 'use', the Bamboo Gentleman could only be used by a Gu Master that has never lied. And to use the Righteous Gu, it needed the Gu Master to have a heart of justice.

Or the Photo-audio Gu, dying after one use, while the visuals could stay on the rock walls for a period of time.

Once the Spring Autumn Cicada is refined, it stays in the aperture and can no longer be moved. This specialty, reminded Fang Yuan of another Gu—The Water Curtain Skyflower.

Chapter 187: There exists one river of time, and the Spring Autumn Cicada acts as the crossing boat

The Water Curtain Skyflower Gu was a Rank four Gu. Once used, it would turn into a giant spherical water shield. The defensive strength of the shield was extremely good and it could even resist attacks from Rank five Gu. However, it had a big weakness; it couldn't be moved and couldn't be stopped. The water shield isolated the inside and outside world, so even the owner couldn't freely enter or exit. Thus, this was used by many forces to protect their territories.

Fang Yuan was not familiar with Spring Autumn Cicada.

In his previous life, he died by the besiegement of the righteous path after just having succeeded in refining the Spring Autumn Cicada; he simply didn't have the time to experiment with it. Also, Spring Autumn Cicada wasn't his vital Gu at the time and this characteristic hadn't revealed itself.

In this life, his cultivation was still low, so he didn't dare to randomly let out the Spring Autumn Cicada.

Spring Autumn Cicada was classified as one of the most unusual Gu and was extremely mysterious. The records of the insights and experiences of its users had never been spread.

Furthermore, once a Gu reaches Rank six and above, they become the only one of their type in the whole world. If someone wanted to refine them, they would only have a probability of success after the previous Gu died, otherwise it was a hundred percent failure.

Thus, this led to Fang Yuan knowing about this characteristic only now.

"Rebirth isn't an easy thing, the Spring and Autumn conceals disaster. Spring Autumn Cicada's recovery speed is increasing more and more, and even the cultivation speed of an A grade aptitude with a sea of resources might not be able to match its speed. Their aperture will sooner or later explode under the pressure of Spring Autumn Cicada!"

Fang Yuan clenched his teeth.

Rebirth was beautiful but possessing Spring Autumn Cicada was equivalent to having half a ten extreme aptitude. It was like being under the execution post where you could be executed at any moment!

"If I can't let Spring Autumn Cicada out, then does that mean I can only use it to rebirth again?" Fang Yuan's frowns deepened.

This appeared to be the only way. A rebirth would mean Spring Autumn Cicada would enter a weak state again, and at the same time, Fang Yuan could escape from this dangerous situation.

This situation seemed to be perfect, but it contained many problems and huge dangers.

First of all, there was no guarantee of the rebirth being successful.

Fang Yuan had gone through rebirth once and he was only able to bring back his valuable experience.

He came to an understanding by integrating the Earth's concept: The world is a three-dimensional space and time is an axis connecting the past and present. Without time, space would be stationary. The movements of every matter was a process, signifying the consumption of time.

There were no parallel dimensions in a world. Using the Spring Autumn Cicada to be reborn was to step across from the latter half of the time axis (future) to some point in the first half (past).

However, Fang Yuan's aged body in the 'future' didn't exist in the 'past'.

Due to the restrictions from the great dao of the world, his body couldn't be brought over to the past, and could only self-detonate. The energy from the self-detonation was a propulsion force and the fragment of the laws of time in Spring Autumn Cicada was like a lone boat which carried Fang Yuan's consciousness from 'future' to be reborn into the 'past'.

Consciousness wasn't a physical matter like a body. Strictly speaking, this 'future' consciousness too, didn't exist in the 'past'.

The ingenuity was contained therein!

'Future' consciousness led to the Gu Master changing himself, and thereby influencing his surroundings. This influence would gradually extend to the whole world; this was the butterfly effect.

When the butterfly effect took place, the world would no longer be the same, causing the existence of the 'future' consciousness to receive the approval of the great dao of the world.

Someone had said that history was like a long river, and a change in an event in the upstream would completely change the downstream.

This mystical world of Gu was like the water in the long river. Almost everyone could only flow along with the stream and go from upstream to downstream. Fang Yuan's consciousness, however, went against the stream, going from downstream to upstream by relying on Spring Autumn Cicada.

When he made changes in the upstream, there would also be changes in the downstream. But the river was still the same river; the world of Gu Masters was still the world of Gu Masters. It was just that history had turned into another corner, bringing another possibility to the equation.

This analogy could be easily understood.

However, Spring Autumn Cicada hadn't recovered completely. It was like a leaky, worn-out boat right now.

Fang Yuan's cultivation was also only Rank three initial stage. There would be an unimaginable difference between the propulsion force of his self-detonation now from the self-detonation of his Rank six cultivation in his previous life. With such a minute force, he simply wouldn't be able to push the Spring Autumn Cicada, let alone flow against the long river of time."I probably won't succeed by trying to rebirth through self-detonation. Who is to say that the broken boat won't be stranded in the long river? And if that happens, my consciousness and memories will be ruthlessly washed away by time. To raise the probability of success, it would be best to wait until the aperture is pushed to the limits, stall for time as much as possible and let Spring Autumn Cicada recover more, decreasing the holes in the worn-out boat. At the same time, increasing my cultivation will provide higher propulsive force to go against the stream, after self-detonation." Fang Yuan heaved a long sigh.

This change in the Spring Autumn Cicada was beyond his anticipation. But with his ever cautious nature, he had a plan ready.The blood bat group was nearing. Fang Yuan, however, had his attention in his aperture.

Yellow-green rays of light flooded his aperture. His white silver Primeval Sea was as still as a mirror under the majestic aura of Spring Autumn Cicada, but there were dangerous cracks in the light membrane of his aperture.

All the other Gu had been suppressed down to the depths of the sea by Spring Autumn Cicada's aura.

Fang Yuan sent his will and a Gu slowly flew towards the surface of the sea, resisting the pressure.

This Gu appeared like a square dice; it was gray and very firm.This was one of the Gu that Fang Yuan had plundered from Bai Ning Bing.

It was a one-time use Gu, and would disappear once used. But its effects were extraordinary, and once used it would completely extract all the strength and potential in a Gu Master's aperture and instantly raise a Gu Master's cultivation to the peak stage of the same rank.

"Stone Aperture Gu, explode."

Fang Yuan willed it; the Stone Aperture Gu immediately exploded, changing into grey powders just like the smoke from a cigarette, and pervaded the Primeval Sea.

The aperture's walls were originally a light membrane, but once this grey powder touched it, the light immediately dimmed down. The powder stuck to the light membrane and the light membrane gradually thickened, experiencing a qualitative change from light to stony.

After several seconds, Fang Yuan's aperture walls had thickened by several times and changed into a heavy, sturdy stone aperture.

The yellow-green radiance of Spring Autumn Cicada still fluctuated continuously, but the aperture could now support its pressure.

Fang Yuan was at Rank three initial stage with light silver primeval essence, and his Primeval Sea shone with light silver light. But right now, his cultivation experienced a sudden rise, leaping from Rank three initial stage to Rank three peak stage, possessing snow silver primeval essence!

"Using the Stone Aperture Gu means cutting off one's advancement route and using up all the potential within the aperture; it will be very difficult to step to Rank four. But, my cultivation has increased and the aperture has turned into stone walls, which is multiple times thicker and firmer than before, and will be able to support the pressure from Spring Autumn Cicada for the time being! Using the Stone Aperture Gu should have been Bai Ning Bing's response to the limits of Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique. Unfortunately, the Ten Extreme Aptitudes are much more troublesome than the Spring Autumn Cicada. Their potential is endless and even by turning one's aperture into stone, the aperture walls will quickly recover."

At this second, the bladewing blood bat group pounced in for the kill.

Fang Yuan gave a cold snort, then took out his Chainsaw Golden Centipede and killed as he retreated.

Fortunately, this tunnel was narrow, and with the Sky Canopy Gu's defense and the Chainsaw Golden Centipede's wide body, Fang Yuan was able to block the blood bat group and stop them from surrounding him.

This greatly reduced their threat.

For a moment, there were only continuous ringing sounds within the tunnel.

The sounds of Chainsaw Golden Centipede's attacks and the sound of bladewing blood bats smashing into the white armor, quickly echoed through the tunnel walls and formed into a medley.

The primeval essence in Fang Yuan's aperture continued to deplete rapidly.

There were close to a hundred blood bats, but without a Gu Master there to control them, there were a lot of internal frictions between the bats and they couldn't form a tacit cooperation. Thus, in reality, Fang Yuan only needed to deal with 30-40 blood bats at the same time.

But even this number wasn't something he could withstand, and he had to retreat while fighting back.

What was even more awkward was that even though he had leaped to Rank three peak stage, his aperture still contained the initial stage light silver primeval essence. Just by relying on his C grade aptitude, the self-production speed of snow silver primeval essence was way too slow. The current situation also didn't allow Fang Yuan to multitask and take out primeval stones to absorb natural primeval essence.

Consuming primeval stones could quickly recover primeval essence, but this method wasn't suitable in a real battle.

Distracting oneself in a life and death battle was asking for humiliation; it was an extremely stupid move and was akin to courting death. At the same time, the efficiency in absorbing natural primeval essence at such a situation was also very low.

This way could only be used during normal cultivation, or to exploit short gaps in battles to quickly recover primeval essence.

Luckily, Fang Yuan obtained a grass gu not long ago: Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus could produce primeval stones; it was very precious and rare. But in fact, this effect was only an expression of its innate ability.

Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was also called 'portable spirit spring' and its innate ability was to produce natural primeval essence. The primeval essence would then condense together to form primeval stones.

The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus that Fang Yuan possessed was lying deep in his Primeval Sea; it appeared like an extremely small spirit spring.

Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus's recipe was created by Immortal Venerable Genesis Lotus.

Only the Gu Masters who have reached Rank nine were respected as venerables. For righteous path, they were called Immortal Venerables; and for demonic path, they were called Demonic Venerables.

Immortal Venerable Genesis Lotus was also known as the the person with the fastest primeval essence recovery speed since the ancient times. In this aspect, he was above other immortal venerables and demonic venerables, and it was all because of the Essence Lotus!

Fang Yuan's Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was only a Rank three and he had just refined it, so it was at its poorest level. But it was already providing a continuous supply of natural primeval essence to Fang Yuan.

The moment this natural primeval essence appeared in Fang Yuan's aperture, it would be automatically refined and turned into snow silver primeval essence.

Supposedly if Fang Yuan absorbed primeval essence from primeval stones, he would still have to divide a part of his mind. But this Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus was his Gu, so using it was as simple and easy as moving his fingers!

Fang Yuan retreated while fighting, and with the assistance of Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, his primeval essence recovery speed could already be comparable with B grade aptitude Gu Masters.

"Kill!"

He gave a fierce shout before abruptly changing his battle style and charging into the blood bat group.

Chainsaw Golden Centipede exploded forth, and its silver sawtooth crazily rotated around, producing screeching sounds as it cut down on a bladewing blood bat hiding in the rear.

This blood bat appeared rather similar to other blood bats, albeit looking a bit more dominant. This was the sole male bat in this blood bat group, and was refined by the first gen Gu Yue. By controlling it, one could indirectly gain control of the whole blood bat group.

Fang Yuan had been secretly planning this attack after careful observation, and made this attack appear unintentional. With the Gu Yue first head not present on the scene, this attack was very effective.

The male bat died on the spot, twisting into a bloody pulp.The remaining female bats immediately scattered!

Chapter 188: Senior paves the way for juniors to run smoothly

In a blood bat group, there was only one male bat, while the rest were all females under the command of the male bat.

Between the male and female bats, they looked the same and did not have difference in appearances. But Fang Yuan was beyond familiar with these bladewing blood bats in his previous life. As long as he had enough time, he could differentiate them.

Without the male bat, the entire group fell into chaos.

Fang Yuan took the chance and waved the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, killing his way through.

A moment later, over twenty bladewing blood bats were decimated, showing Fang Yuan's resolution of battle.

But the intense battle also caused Fang Yuan's primeval essence in his aperture to decrease tremendously.

"Time to go!" Fang Yuan decisively retreated, running away at full force.

When the blood bat group behind him reacted, Fang Yuan was already a hundred steps away. About twenty bladewing blood bats continued to chase after him while the others flew in all directions.

"Gasp gasp..." In the narrow tunnel, Fang Yuan breathed hard while sprinting, activating the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

After an intense battle, the snow silver primeval essence left in his aperture as well as the low Primeval Sea level gradually rose back up.

The longer time passed, the faster Fang Yuan's battle strength recovered.

Suddenly, Fang Yuan's thunderwings flapped, and the force dragged his entire body forward, almost letting him crash into the cave walls.

The Thunderwings Gu had been polluted by the Blood Frenzy Gu, and it had reached its limits, starting to show signs of being uncontrollable.

"Very soon, the Thunderwings Gu will turn into a pool of blood water and turn into a new pollution source." Thinking so, Fang Yuan stopped hesitating and activated it three times, finally causing the disobeying Thunderwings Gu to detach from his back.

"Go." Fang Yuan resolutely gave up the Thunderwings Gu, throwing it behind him.

The bladewing blood bat group behind him surrounded the Thunderwings Gu completely. They rushed up, tearing the Thunderwings Gu into bits.

This obstruction gave Fang Yuan a little bit of time to recover.

Until the bladewing blood bats caught up to Fang Yuan, the primeval essence in his aperture had already recovered over half of the total.

The snow silver primeval essence compared to the light silver primeval essence, had several times more sustainability, and Fang Yuan's current battle strength had greatly exceeded an initial stage.

He laughed heartily, waving the Chainsaw Golden Centipede to fight once again.

After killing around 8-9 of them, the rest all flew and escaped.

"Unfortunately I do not have a Gu like the iron hand grappling Gu. The bladewing blood bat Gu flies too fast, and its wings are sharp like blades, it is really hard to capture. If I can capture two or three, that would be nice."

Fang Yuan kept the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, and turned around towards the deeper part of the cave.When he snatched the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, he was engulfed by the blood water. That was definitely caused by the first gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue used the Blood Wight Gu, turning into a flying zombie. His aperture was long dead and could no longer recover primeval essence. Unless he used primeval stones, his primeval essence in the aperture would be limited by the amount left inside.

But if he had a Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, to a large extent, he could negate this weakness.

Thus, not long ago, he sent two groups of bladewing blood bats towards Fang Yuan, attempting to capture him. Thankfully, Fang Yuan saw something amiss and turned around in time. At the same time, Tie Xue Leng indirectly helped him with the soundwave.

"I wonder how's the battle between Tie Xue Leng and First gen Gu Yue." Fang Yuan gaze was concentrated.

No matter which side won, they would still target him.

Tie Xue Leng wants to bring him to justice, while First gen Gu Yue wants the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus.

Although the bladewing blood bats had dispersed, Fang Yuan's danger was still unresolved.

"I have to leave Qing Mao mountain immediately, as soon as possible!" Fang Yun gritted his teeth. He could no longer return, only able to walk along this mountain cave, trying to find a way out.

This cave was obviously man-made, but after a long time, many areas had collapsed.

Fang Yuan continued to advance, and when he met these dead ends he could only use the Chainsaw Golden Centipede.The Chainsaw Golden Centipede was originally an underground creature, adept at digging holes, so at this time it had a great use.

Fang Yuan also had the strength of two boars, and he dug through the soil and continued forward.

This greatly reduced his speed, and after three to four hours, he finally got to the end of the cave.

A large sturdy rock wall blocked his path completely.

Even the Chainsaw Golden Centipede couldn't drill its way through.

"Did the First gen Gu Yue seal this cave completely already?" Fang Yuan's heart sank.

Bam!

The two sides' palms met, and the Xiong clan Gu Master flew into the air like a rag, landing heavily on the ground.

Cough

The Xiong clan Gu Master coughed out a mouthful of blood, falling unconscious.

In the sky, the sun was shining brightly, sending down scorching rays of light. The sunlight shone over the wilderness, and the light reflected on Bai Zhong Shui's fat face.

This young Bai clan Gu Master laughed smugly, "Hmph, so what if you're the Xiong clan Gu Master? Daring to compete strength with me!"

She moved her fat 'slim body', trying to finish off her opponent and take the token, but suddenly a moonblade came attacking.

Bam!

Bai Zhong Shui's body turned, shooting a water ball from her mouth.

The water ball and moonblade collided, exploding together.

Three Gu Masters with Fang Zheng as the lead, jumped down from the branches.

"Gu Yue clan's people, this is my battle reward." Bai Zhong Shui squinted, her eyes showing a dangerous light.

Fang Zheng's strangely bloodshot eyes stared at Bai Zhong Shui intently as he said, "So what? Now YOU are our prey!"

At another side of the forest, more footsteps were heard.

A few people walked out from the shadows; it was Xiong clan's genius youngster Xiong Lin. his bald head reflected the sunlight, causing him to shine like a diamond.

"Hehehe, this has gotten interesting!" Bai Zhong Shui laughed loudly, but the next moment her laughter stopped.

The two sides attacked together, causing Bai Zhong Shui to be caught off guard, getting surrounded.

Bai Zhong Shui coughed out some blood, her expression turning ugly, "What? Gu Yue clan, you are cooperating with these despicable Xiong clan people?"

Fang Zheng was expressionless, his killing intent raging, not saying a word and getting closer to Bai Zhong Shui.

Xiong Lin laughed, "This battle concerns the three clans' demographics for the next hundred years, so let me tell you. Gu Yue clan has already established an alliance with our Xiong clan. Bai Zhong Shui, today is your death date."

"Spit!" Bai Zhong Shui coughed out a mouth of blood water as she stared at her surroundings in disdain, "So what if I die? Heh, ganging up... you are just afraid of our Bai Ning Bing. It's useless, this is only the initial battle, there will still be 1 versus 1 later. Is there anyone in your clans that can fight against Bai Ning Bing? We are destined to be number one!"

"Hehehe, thus we decided that in this first battle, we shall cooperate and finish off Bai Ning Bing!" Xiong Lin laughed loudhly.

buzzbuzzbuzz

Chainsaw Golden Centipede's razors grinded against the rock wall, causing a loud noise to echo in the cave.

This rock wall was sturdy and thick, being very weird. Fang Yuan's forehead was full of sweat, as he used the Chainsaw Golden Centipede and Blood Moon Gu to attack in turns, but even after many hours, he only progressed about 50cm.

"Is it really the end for me... eh?" Fang Yuan's heart moved, suddenly feeling that there was a lifeform in the rock wall.

He quickly used the Earth Communication Ear Grass Gu, listening to the rock wall. There was a mysterious lifeform on the other side of the rock wall, but its aura was very weak.

Half an hour later, Fang Yuan dug a hole, ad the mysterious life form showed itself.

Its entire body was pitch black, emitting a metallic glow like iron and steel. Both its chest and back armor were thick lines that showed a dominating aura. It had three pairs of legs, each having spiral shaped feelers at the tip. It caused Fang Yuan to think of the spiral tip of an electric drill.

"It's the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider!" Fang Yuan was enlightened, immediately thinking of the Flower Wine Monk.

The questions in Fang Yuan's heart were mostly answered at this point.

Back then the Flower Wine Monk, in order to nurture the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, came to the Gu Yue village. But at the last moment, he was stopped by First gen Gu Yue, thus he used his methods to throw it into the blood river graveyard.The Flower Wine Monk was also a Rank five Gu Master, he had to have an intense battle with First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue had operated for hundreds of years, having terrain advantage, so the Flower Wine Monk could not compete against him, thus he could only escape.

He used the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider to dig out this path, and after leaving the battlefield he had already suffered an incurable injury. At the end of his life, he hurriedly left behind his inheritance as a last act of revenge. He attempted to let his descendants take the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus and ruin the Gu Yue clan's foundation.

This explains why the Flower Wine Monk was bathed in blood, his body full of injuries.

But the reason for why the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider fall into slumber and seal itself here, that was still a mystery. Also the First gen Gu Yue, what in the world was he after?

"These suspicions are all minute details. What's important is leaving this place!" Fang Yuan stretched out his hand, sending out some primeval essence and refining the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider.

This sturdy rock wall was the cocoon created by the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider when it fell into hibernation. It was extremely weak, like the White Boar Gu that Fang Yuan took out from the Earth Treasury Flower Gu.

Thus, even though it was Rank five, Fang Yuan easily refined it.

Fang Yuan threw the Thunderwings Gu away earlier and was lacking a movement-type Gu, this being his weakness once again. But now he obtained the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider, so it was like a glimmer of hope in the darkest hour.This Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider was a large steed-type Gu. It ate soil as food, and was easy to raise.

Fang Yuan injected his snow silver primeval essence into it, and the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider gradually awakened, its aura becoming stronger.

It started to consume, eating large amounts of soil.

When it recovered to an extent, Fang Yuan who couldn't wait to leave quickly got onto its back, ordering it to move forward.

Although it had only recovered a little, the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider was still a Rank five Gu. Its three pairs of legs moved quickly, dashing through.

After the cocoon broke, the cave behind was exposed too.

This path was the one the Flower Wine Monk created when he escaped. Seniors pave the way for juniors to run along, so this greatly helped Fang Yuan.

The only worry was, steed-type Gu worms took a lot of primeval essence to use.

The Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider was Rank five. Rank three primeval essence could not sustain its expenditure, so every now and then, Fang Yuan had to stop and sit on the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's back, activating the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus while extracting natural essence from his primeval stones.

With two sources, as well as his C grade natural recovery, Fang Yuan's primeval essence recovery rate was fast, incomparable to before.

As he instructed the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider to move forward, he would also stop to recover his primeval essence. When they encountered a cave-in, they would drill their way through, and with such a repeated process, Fang Yuan gradually moved away from the blood lake graveyard, going towards the surface.

Chapter 189: Shocking change

The sun lowers as night descends, and the setting sun was like a burning fire on the horizon.

Standing on a slope was Bai Ning Bing, clothed in white, his hair snowy white. The setting sun's last rays reflected in his eyes, hinting that his life was ending."Such a beautiful sunset, how many more times can I see it... this brilliance of nature, I have only seen a little of them all, what a waste. Especially when around me, these annoying fellows are still arguing."

Bai Ning Bing snorted in his heart, retracting his gaze and sweeping the environment.

Gu Yue and Xiong clan's alliance, the remaining hundred Gu Masters gathered together and surrounded Bai Ning Bing.

"Bai Ning Bing, if you back out of this competition now, we can spare your life!"

"Indeed, if you know your place, we might as well be kind and let you off."

"Your Bai clan Gu Masters are mostly finished. The remaining ones have all been stopped by us. Don't rest your hopes on reinforcements, they will not come!"

With Fang Zheng, Xiong Jiao Man, Xiong Lin and Chi Cheng as leaders, the young Gu Masters spoke in turns, trying to break Bai Ning Bing's spirits.

But these words, Bai Ning Bing did not put to heart.

"A bunch of rats coming to the elephant and screaming, how pathetically laughable," Bai Ning Bing laughed coldly, his gaze sweeping across the crowd, showing disdain. "Among you people, only Gu Yue Fang Yuan is slightly interesting. Too bad he isn't here. Hehe, come at me together."

Saying so, Bai Ning Bing created an iceblade, using his hand to wipe the sharp blade that emitted cold energy; he did not even look at the people around him.

"This person is too arrogant!"

"Hmph, not taking us seriously!"

"Brothers, let's attack together. Everyone send out one attack, even ten Bai Ning Bings will be turned into meat paste!"

The Gu Masters jeered, but no one dared to attack rashly.

Although Bai Ning Bing was alone, his aura was overwhelming, causing everyone to feel threatened.

"Everyone calm down, don't listen to Bai Ning Bing's taunts. We did not practice together before and do not have good cooperation. If we attack together, we will waste much of our efforts and he will take advantage of it." Xiong Lin shouted.

"Then who attacks first?" Chi Cheng asked.

Although they cooperated with Xiong clan and attacked the Bai clan, this alliance was not a close one. Whoever attacks first bears higher risks, and also risks the other party taking advantage of their combat.

"Nevermind, I'll engage Bai Ning Bing first. To be honest, I've wanted to fight you some long ago." Xiong Jian Man took a step forward.

She blew a whistle, and once she did, sounds of beasts stampeding could be heard from afar. Many blacks shadows overlapped in the forest, and what showed up was over two hundred black bears!

The black bear at the front of the horde was larger than the rest; it was a hundred beast king level black bear.

The wolf tide was dangerous, but it was also an opportunity. Xiong Jiao Man rose to Rank three because of it, and the Bear Enslavement Gu also rose to Rank three, finally being able to enslave bear-type hundred beast kings!

This was Xiong Jiao Man's trump card.

"Way to go, lady boss!"

"Oh my god~, so many bears."

"With all these bears and us being around a hundred people, Bai Ning Bing is dead meat!"

Xiong clan Gu Masters were stirred, getting excited. Gu Yue clan looked complicated; after Xiong Li died, this Xiong Jiao Man became the number one contender in the Xiong clan. Looking at Gu Yue clan, after Qing Shu died, Mo Bei followed as well. Although Fang Yuan rose to Rank three, his aptitude is only C grade, it was hard to count on him.

"Thankfully, we still have the A grade Gu Yue Fang Zheng!" Many Gu Masters looked at Fang Zheng, thinking so and feeling assured.

Especially during this three-clan competition, Fang Zheng seemed to have gotten more mature, attacking more ferociously, and many Bai clan Gu Masters were killed by him. Such a performance caused many clansmen to feel comforted.

This was the true disposition of a A grade genius!

"The results are pretty much assured. Even a Rank three peak stage with much talent cannot be the match for a hundred people. Lord Qing Shu, I will take revenge for you personally!! After that, if brother appears..." Fang Zheng stared intently at Bai Ning Bing, thinking rapidly in his mind.

"Merely a hundred beast king, what a boring trick."

His entire body was emitting cold air.

"Northern Dark Ice Soul physique... I'm at my limit already huh." Bai Ning Bing felt his life ending; his body had reached some sort of limit. Not soon after, he would die. Even now, he could feel his body starting to collapse, and much of his flesh and blood was turning into ice and snow.

But even so, Bai Ning Bing remained calm, his gaze concentrated. He took a final look at the sun's rays, before turning around and looking at the charging bear group.

"Since you are all looking for death, I shall act mercifully and grant you all your wishes. Maybe this way, it can bring some excitement to my life," he sighed softly.

Not far away, the three clan leaders and Gu Masters stood still, completely silent.

"The battle is finally starting! Killing Bai Ning Bing is the greatest victory!" Xiong clan leader was secretly excited.

"Hmph, we were tricked. They actually ganged up to deal with us. Hehehe, you have all underestimated Bai Ning Bing, get ready for a shock." Bai clan leader was calm as water, plotting in his mind.

Gu Yue Bo showed a worried expression.

Up until now, Fang Yuan and Tie Xue Leng did not show up at all.

Although the three-clan competition was important, his mind was elsewhere.

"Desolate Yin Ancient Moon physique... If Fang Yuan really has such an aptitude, we have to protect him at all costs and bring him into the blood lake graveyard!" Thinking so, Gu Yue Bo looked at Tie Ruo Nan without turning his body.This Tie family young lady had a strong background, but she was already brought around by Gu Yue Bo, secretly a captive.

Tie Ruo Nan was not worried about her situation. She believed her father, and was also thinking about how to capture Fang Yuan.

Whatever aptitude Fang Yuan had, as long as one bothered to, they could assess it. If he really was a ten extreme talent, then his suspicion would be the greatest!

"Fuck!" Fang Yuan cursed, lying on the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's back, sticking closely and preventing himself from falling off.

He wanted to use the Flower Wine Monk's opened path to advance easily.

But good times do not last, for not long after, the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider started to go crazy.

It started to absorb the natural essence in the air, using it. At the same time, its three pairs of legs started to dig out new paths, moving around randomly in the underground cave.

Fang Yuan understood finally.

This Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider, under the Flower Wine Monk's command, had engaged in battle with First gen Gu Yue previously.

In the battle, it was corrupted by the Blood Frenzy Gu.

The Flower Wine Monk relied on it to escape, then hurriedly created the secret cave, leaving behind his inheritance before dying.

Upon losing its master, the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider lost control and frantically went back to that path that it had dug when escaping.

Right before death, what was fortunate was that the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider sealed itself and fell into hibernation, preserving its last life force before dying.

Hundreds of years later, Fang Yuan returned to the place and dug out the cocoon, causing it to awaken again. But the Blood Frenzy Gu's problem was not solved, and thus after a while, it started to act up again.Fang Yuan was deep in the cave, and just by relying on his own strength he could not escape to the surface. He needed the ability of the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider.

The Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider started to go crazy, getting more uncontrollable; Fang Yuan could only ride on its back, betting on his luck.

But at this point, the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's frequency of going crazy was not so high, so Fang Yuan still had some control of it.

Although his control was slipping, overall, he still controlled the general direction. He let the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider dig its way to the surface, but where it would end up, Fang Yuan had no idea.

The last of the sun's rays were like blood, reflecting on the minced corpses and broken limbs everywhere on the battlefield.

Bai Ning Bing stood arrogantly on the battlefield, a thick layer of ice beneath his feet as the icy domain continued to spread outwards.

The remaining Gu Masters amounted to less than thirty, staying closely together trying to find a bit of assurance from each other's body warmth.

The bear group had long been exterminated. Even Xiong Jian Man had been beheaded by Bai Ning Bing's iceblade, and her head flew far away as blood poured like a fountain out of her neck.

Xiong Lin was penetrated by the icicles from Bai Ning Bing, and Gu Yue Chi Cheng was turned into a ice sculpture. In the ice coffin, he still retained the dodging action right before death, his face showing shock, fear, and utter shock, vivid and lifelike.

Fang Zheng's body was full of injuries, but there was no blood; his injuries were all frozen by the ice and snow.

He breathed roughly, looking at Bai Ning Bing in disbelief. What happened earlier was like a nightmare!

Bai Ning Bing was definitely a Rank three, but his battle strength was almost Rank four!!

"Hmph, although lookalikes, but you are not him, how boring...." Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Zheng, walking closer. Fang Zheng still being alive, was also intentional by Bai Ning Bing.

The Gu Masters all got into a commotion, their morale at its lowest. If not for the fact that their clan leaders were watching from afar, they would've broken down and escaped for their lives already.

"Damn it, damn it! Why is our battle strength so different, I am an A grade talent, am I going to die here?" Fang Zheng gritted his teeth, screaming in his heart.

"Die." Bai Ning Bing jumped, raising his iceblade high while in mid-air.

SLASH!

The iceblade expanded, almost five to six times of the original, sending an unblockable aura as it slashed towards everyone.

"I am going to die!"

"Ahhhhh..."Facing this attack, many Gu Masters broke down and cried in despair.

"Fuck, why did it come to this!" Xiong clan leader's face was full of despair.

Gu Yue Bo was urging to move, but Bai clan leader snickered, stopping him, "Gu Yue clan leader, no one is to interfere, are you going to turn on your word and break the agreement?"

Gu Yue Bo squinted his eyes, "Bai Ning Bing is only Rank three, he cannot have such strength, you are cheating blatantly!"

"Cheating? Hehe, let me tell you the truth, our clan's Bai Ning Bing is the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique!" Bai clan leader shouted loudly.

"What? Ten extreme aptitude!" At once, Gu Yue Bo and Xiong clan leader were shocked.

"Reporting! Clan leader, there has been a strange earthquake, many of the clan's bamboo buildings have collapsed, and the ground is seeping with blood water. Not many people are injured but they are flustered," A Gu Yue clan Gu Master came running.

"To think that there is a thing!" Gu Yue Bo's expression changed.

Chapter 190: Third battle against Bai Ning Bing

"Moon Raiment!" With the blade impending, Fang Zheng shouted, activating his Gu worm. A misty light that was blue like the moon gushed out from his body, extending and surrounding all the Gu Masters around him.

But even so, everyone was still in despair."Struggling is useless." Bai Ning Bing's blue eyes shone with cruelty and indifference.

But at this time!

Bam!The ground under everyone's feet suddenly grew and turned into a lump before exploding, sending soil flying.

Gu Masters cried painfully as they rolled away from the impact.

In a cloud of smoke, a giant spider emerged from everyone's sights.

The aura of a Rank five Gu made everyone wary.

On the spider that looked like it was made of steel, a black clothed, black haired young man was standing upright.

"I finally reached the surface!" Fang Yuan clenched his fist, his eyes emitting a brilliant glow!

"Eh?" Soon after, he saw Bai Ning Bing who was hacking towards him in mid-air.

The giant iceblade cut through the winds as it slashed towards him.

"Fang Yuan, you are finally here!" Bai Ning Bing's calm face, after a slight stun, completely transformed into one of excitement and battle intent.Fang Yuan snorted before the iceblade touched him. The icy winds caused him to feel a slight chill as his black hair flew behind him.

He raised his hand, the Chainsaw Golden Centipede!

Bam!Iceblade collided with the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, and after a stalemate, the golden centipede's razors rotated furiously, large amounts of ice shards flying out.

[Friction noises]

Cracks quickly emerged from the surface of the iceblade, quickly covering its entire body."Break!" Fang Yuan shouted; he had the strength of two boars, his strength completely overwhelmed Bai Ning Bing.

Bai Ning Bing could only let go as the iceblade broke into pieces, and ice shards fell.

The Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider began to go berserk again, spreading its six legs and attacking towards Bai Ning Bing.Gu worms had low intellect, but they were born sensitive, able to sense which target was more of a threat to them. Bai Ning Bing's aura caused the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider to treat him as an enemy, locking onto him.

Bai Ning Bing's arms waved, and icicles flew out in a row. The icicles hit the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's body and shattered, while the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider went berserk and growled, pouncing while Fang Yuan was on it.

Swish swish swish!Three black spiral legs shot out like an arrow towards Bai Ning Bing's fragile body.

Sensing danger, a snowy light shot out from Bai Ning Bing's aperture.

The light expanded, revealing the white form immortal snake Gu, floating in mid-air.Bai Ning Bing laughed heartily, leaping and landing on the white form immortal snake's back, staring at Fang Yuan, "Interesting! Very interesting! Fang Yuan, you didn't let me down after all!"

"B-Big... brother..." Fang Zheng climbed up from the floor. His face had been cut by the iceblade, his face full of blood as he stared at Fang Yuan with a complex expression.

"The opponent has a Rank five Gu as well?" Bai clan leader's gaze tightened, becoming nervous.

"Fang Yuan, you finally appeared! Rank five Gu... isn't that the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider?" Gu Yue Bo's attention was attracted.

On the battlefield, two youngsters of different ages stood on opposing sides.

One wore white robes, had silver hair and blue eyes, riding on the white form immortal snake holding an iceblade in his hand, like a ice immortal descending to the mortal realm.

The other had black robes, black hair and black eyes, standing on the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's back, having the Chainsaw Golden Centipede in his hand, buzzing as it rotated, like a demon god summoned into the world.

The two's opposing stances attracted many gazes.

Bai Ning Bing had an excited expression, raising the iceblade, shouting loudly, "This will be the most exciting battle in my life. Come, Fang Yuan, let us battle to the death!"

"Hmph." Fang Yuan stared at Bai Ning Bing, using his peripheral vision to observe the surroundings.

This was the three clans' competition.To think that the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider brought him here...

He did not want to engage with Bai Ning Bing and waste his time here. Whether Tie Xue Leng or the First gen Gu Yue wins, they would definitely hunt him down. But if he does not defeat this Bai Ning Bing, how could he escape?

Thus battle it is!BAM!

White form immortal snake and Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider collided. The white snake coiled as the black spider stabbed, fighting at close range.

On the two Gu's backs, two bodies moved about, the iceblade drawing different sparks in the sky while the Chainsaw Golden Centipede buzzed as it extended and contracted at will.The mountain rocks broke, and thunderous explosions happened continuously.

Icicles hit Fang Yuan directly, but were blocked by the white armor of the Sky Canopy Gu. Blood moonblade hit Bai Ning Bing, causing a large injury that was instantly covered by a layer of frost, sealing the wound. The frost turned into blood and flesh, causing Bai Ning Bing to recover completely."It really is the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique!" Xiong clan leader saw this and stared with his eyes wide open.

Ten extreme physiques were legendary aptitudes, he did not think he would see one with his own eyes.

"Hehehe, Fang Yuan dares to attempt to fight Bai Ning Bing, he is assured to lose!" Bai clan leader laughed sinisterly.

"That might not be..." Tie Ruo Nan beside him pouted.

"Ten extreme physique, it has to be it. In such a battle, if he was a C grade, his primeval essence would've been long gone! Fang Yuan, you are indeed the Desolate Yin Ancient Moon physique!" Gu Yue Bo clenched his fist, his expression extremely agitated.

"This is brother's true power? So brother really is a ten extreme physique, he's been concealing himself this entire time!" Fang Zheng's mouth was slightly open, his face full of dejection.

The truth was in front of him, so what does his previous pride amount to now?

Everytime, Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing's intense clashes would cause his heart to tremble once.He felt himself getting smaller, and his older brother Fang Yuan's shadow started to enshroud him once again.

"What sort of battle is this! I cannot believe that this is two Rank three Gu Masters fighting!"

"Did I see wrongly? Fang Yuan is so ferocious? Fighting one on one against Bai Ning Bing and being equally matched!"

Some surviving young Gu Masters stared in disbelief.

The battle suddenly shifted once again.

White form immortal snake and the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider both took great damage, but it was not refined by Bai Ning Bing, merely attracted by the Northern Dark Ice Soul physique.

White form immortal snake spit out a lump of white fog, covering the entire battlefield. Then, its body trembled and it threw Bai Ning Bing off its body before leaving.

"This, immortal..." Seeing this, Bai clan leader was shocked. As he watched the escaping white snake, he did not know what to say.This fog was like a maze, able to obscure vision and follow one like a shadow. Fang Yuan was covered by the white fog, and his eyes saw nothing but whiteness.

But he did not panic, as although his vision was affected, he still had his other four senses—taste, hearing, smell and touch.

Earth Communication Ear grass.

Roots grew out of Fang Yuan's ears, and very soon he heard a sound analyzing the situation within three hundred steps of his radius.

Lightning Eye Gu!

Bai Ning Bing's eyes shone with lightning. Although Lightning Eye Gu was Rank three and could break through illusions, this fog made by a Rank five immortal snake completely suppressed it.

"Fuck!" He cursed loudly.

Icicle Gu!Dozens of icicles flew out in all directions.

Fang Yuan's ears twitched, hearing the sound of the icicles moving against the wind. Thus, he hurriedly flipped his body to the other side of the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider.

Bam bam bam.The icicles struck the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider's body, causing it to go into a rage and rush towards the direction of the icicles.

"I'm not going to play with you." Fang Yuan got off the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider, abandoning it and relying on the Earth Communication Ear grass and attempting to leave the battlefield.

This Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider had already been corrupted by the Blood Frenzy Gu, about to turn into a pool of blood water soon, so he should abandon it as soon as possible.

That Bai Ning Bing was now a ticking time bomb, and killing him is akin to setting off a bomb, he cannot be touched.

The Gu Masters observing the battle only saw a lump of mist, before a small piece was divided out and floated towards the southeast direction of the battlefield.

Within this mist, it was naturally Fang Yuan.

The maze fog followed like a shadow, and unless dispelled, it would continue to obscure Fang Yuan's vision until the maze fog fades on its own.

Fang Yuan's eyes continued to see nothing but fog, but he had the Earth Communication Ear grass, thus he could determine his location through sound.

The moving wind and tree leaves, the mountain springs and its flowing water, the chirping of the birds, the breathing of the wild beasts, these were all sounds. Only the mountain rocks had no sound, thus, he sometimes knocked into them.

"Iceblade storm!" Behind him, Bai Ning Bing's voice came.

Huff huff huff...

The winds blew as cold air spread, the temperature in the air started to decrease, and the white colored iceblade storm was formed, even bigger than before.

Even the Thousand Li Earthwolf Spider was repelled by it.

"That lump of mist, it should be Fang Yuan! Quickly stop him!!" Beside, Tie Ruo Nan shouted loudly.

"Fang Yuan, don't go, Gu Yue village is your home!" Gu Yue Bo was anxious, trying to chase after him but was stopped by the other two clan leaders.

"Why? Gu Yue clan leader, are you going to break the agreement and enter the battlefield?" Xiong clan leader crossed his arms and snickered.

"Hmph, our Gu Yue clan admits our loss for this battle. Now, whoever stops me, I will murder without hesitation!" Gu Yue Bo watched as Fang Yuan got even further, as his anxiety rose.

"Are you threatening me? I am not scared of you, Gu Yue Bo." Bai clan leader's expression was grim, at the same time signalling to his Gu Masters.

The Gu Master understood, and immediately dispatched his men to chase after Fang Yuan.

"We cannot let him escape, I'm going ahead." Tie Ruo Nan seeing this chance, immediately moved, a pair of black steel wings emerging from her back as she flew into mid-air, chasing after Fang Yuan.

But at this time, a green shadow shot over.Rank five—Giant mountain puppet Gu!

This Gu looked like a bronze mask. Its appearance was simple, only showing both eyes and mouth. The bronze mask was covered in blood, flying towards the young girl's face disregarding her shock.

"Father!" Seeing the blood traces, Tie Ruo Nan screamed subconsciously.

At this time, a large steel hand flew over as well, grabbing Tie Ruo Nan and flying far away without a moment of pause.

This sudden change caused everyone to be taken aback.

"It seems Tie Xue Leng is most likely going to lose. Hehe, it has been almost a thousand years, senior brother. You have really brought me, your junior brother, some surprise." Over 300 metres above the ground, an elderly Gu Master stared at the scene, his expression calm and indifferent.

His hair was white, and so were his eyebrows. As he sat on a giant crane, his right palm opened with a Kinship Blood worm Gu.This Gu was crystal clear, like a red agate. Its shape was like a cicada, emitting a glow at times, pointing towards the Gu Yue village.

"Senior brother, even if you hide here, I can still find you. You stole my opportunity back then, so I will return the favor to you a thousand fold this time!"

The white brow elderly gritted his teeth as he said so, and he showed an expression of utter hatred.

Chapter 191: Crane disaster

In the azure blue sky, numerous clouds were floating aimlessly.The elderly Gu Master rode on top of the white crane. Under his white eyebrows that were sharp like daggers, his eyes revealed a deep killing intent.

"Hehehe, with this grudge of mine, I shall start taking revenge on your descendants," he laughed, staring down at the battlefield, stretching his thin and dry finger and pointing downwards.

The white crane below him raised its long and elegant neck, crying out in a bright and loud voice.

The voice spread through the skies, and from far away, there were many return calls.

"What sound is this?" Fang Yuan was activating the Earth Communication Ear grass at the time, thus he heard it first and was shocked in his heart.The crane cries went on endlessly, all at different pitches, giving off an impressive magnitude. This was not over a hundred canes, nor a few thousand crying at once; it was the collective cries of over ten thousand flying cranes that could cause such an effect.

"Is there a migrating flock of cranes nearby?" Out of nowhere, Fang Yuan felt a strong sense of danger.

The crane cries attracted the attention of the Gu Masters in the arena, turning their heads to look at them.

"What's that in the sky?"

"From the sound, I'd say its a large herd of migrating birds. Tell all the Gu Masters not to attack recklessly and bring trouble upon themselves!" Bai clan leader was just saying, but suddenly he came to a halt.

His eyes dilated, seeing one, two, three... almost ten thousand cranes in the sky, clumped together and attacking towards the arena.

"How can this be?""Get your guard on, defend!"

"Let's escape, there are ten thousand cranes here, there has to be a myriad beast king."

"The wolf tide is just over, now we have a crane disaster? Oh Heavens, Qing Mao Mountain is truly a place of disasters."

Gu Masters started commenting, expressing the shock in their hearts as their spirits wavered.

After finally resisting the wolf tide, a crane disaster appears. The three clans on Qing Mao mountain have suffered great losses already, how could they have the excess energy to deal with such a large flock of cranes?The flying cranes folded back their wings, shooting down like a rain of arrows.

Under the thunderous cries, screams of fear, pain and horror erupted at once, as all sorts of lights burst forth—moonblades, water balls and steel spikes were sent into the skies.

After a momentary resistance, more than half of the Gu Masters were killed.

These flying cranes were like pile drivers; each time their wings flapped, it had the strength of a boar, and their claws were sharp and could break rocks. Ordinary cranes were hard enough to deal with, not to mention the large amounts of hundred and thousand beast kings among them.

The clans had centuries of experience in dealing with the wolf tide, and also the sturdy villages that can defend against them. But here, it was the wilderness with no buildings in sight. Where could they find anything resembling a fort?

Thus, during the first attack, half the Gu Masters passed away.The cranes' long beaks penetrated hearts, their claws grabbing onto skulls. With a flap of their wings, people would vomit blood and be sent flying, all their bones broken.

Fang Yuan was also attacked. his eyes could only see white fog as he relied on the Earth Communication Ear grass to avoid their attacks.

"Fang Yuan, hang in there!" This time, he heard Gu Yue Bo shouting behind him.

Fang Yuan felt puzzled.

What's up with this Gu Yue Bo, when he shouted Fang Yuan's name earlier, the tone was weird, like he had intentions to protect him. Now he even ran over to help.

Fang Yuan was a scheming old fox, but even he could not predict everything. In this short period, how could he conjecture that Tie Ruo Nan assumed he was a ten extreme physique?

Gu Yue Bo was a Rank four expert, thus since the cranes attacking Fang Yuan were ordinary beasts, they were easily killed or repelled by him.

"Fang Yuan, is that you?" Gu Yue Bo came to the maze fog.

Fang Yuan's thoughts whirled in his mind: Right now, his predicament was extremely dangerous, and being near Gu Yue Bo would greatly increase his chances of survival. Thus he answered: "It's me."

Gu Yue Bo hearing Fang Yuan's voice, finally breathed a sigh of relief, "Very good! Fang Yuan, let's not mention what happened in the past. No matter what, the clan will protect your safety. Let's return to the village, I'll protect you while retreating!"

What he did not know was that the village was the most dangerous location for Fang Yuan right now.

But the crane disaster was a much greater threat compared to the village. At least if he went back to the village, he would not die immediately compared to staying under the cranes' attacks.

Fang Yuan sighed without hesitating, "Please lead the way clan leader, I will try to keep up!"

But at this time, a giant crane descended from the sky. The white-brow old Gu Master sat on top of the crane, his tone cold, "No one can escape, all of you shall die here."

Fang Yuan could not see, but heard Gu Yue Bo beside him shout, "Rank five Gu Master!"

Evidently, the Gu Yue clan leader had investigative methods that was able to deduce the stranger's cultivation level.Fang Yuan was stunned in his heart: Where is there another Rank five Gu Master here? This tiny Qing Mao mountain, it was neither a famous location nor full of resources, why are all the Rank five experts gathering here?

"Don't tell me, this has to do with First gen Gu Yue?" Fang Yuan hit an inspiration.

His heart jumped!

If it was an ordinary crane disaster, he would have no chances left. Wild flying beasts were hard to make use of, and although he was at Rank three peak stage, compared to a Rank five he was still weak and could not get out of the danger.

But now another Rank five Gu Master showed up. Not only is he another source of extreme danger, but also a chance to break out of his predicament.

This current Qing Mao mountain, the three Rank five experts were the crucial players, the rest were insignificant.

Only a Rank five can deal with Rank five.

Immediately, Fang Yuan decided in his heart.

It is time, he has to bet on this!

"Clan leader, the First gen ancestor has fully awakened, we will be safe if we return to the village!" Fang Yuan said.

"What?" Gu Yue Bo shouted in shock.

His shock gave Fang Yuan reassurance."I won't lie about such things. As long as we get back to the village, we can save our lives," Fang Yuan continued.

Gu Yue Bo was a resolute man, thus he brought Fang Yuan and sped towards the village.

But the flying cranes continued to approach, blocking the path. Hundred beast kings and thousand beast kings appeared non-stop.

Gu Yue Bo fought with his life, protecting Fang Yuan. Eventually he could no longer proceed, falling into the encirclement of the flying cranes. Fang Yuan was protected by Gu Yue Bo, thus he was safe for the time being.

Once time was up, the maze fog vanished.

Fang Yuan observed the battlefield, only to see corpses lying everywhere, showing that a terrifying battle had happened. The Gu Masters' sacrifice was huge, but the flock of cranes were also greatly damaged. Other than broken limbs of humans, there were also crane corpses everywhere.

"Isn't this the Iron Beak Flying Crane?" Fang Yuan felt puzzled.

Others might not recognise it, for after all, this flying beast was not from the Southern Border. But he knew that this Iron Beak Flying Crane originated from the Middle Kingdom.

"Eh? Myriad beast king, Rank five expert!" Next, Fang Yuan saw in mid-air, a giant crane was flapping its wings, floating. On its back, a white-brow white haired old man was sitting with a cold expression.

Fang Yuan looked away, back at Gu Yue Bo.

This Gu Yue clan leader was already full of injuries, his body full of blood, fighting with his life. Many times he could clearly have avoided, but to protect Fang Yuan, he would rather suffer the injury himself.

"Clan leader! The current situation is not looking good. Gu Masters are fighting bravely, but are all divided into different areas by the flying cranes, they will eventually get overwhelmed. We must gather their strength into one. Only then can we have a chance to break out of this and return to the village!" Fang Yuan said to Gu Yue Bo.

"You are right." Gu Yue Bo looked across the battlefield, shouting loudly, "Everyone, the enemy is before us, our Gu Yue village has a method to deal with the enemy, quickly assemble with me and kill our way out!"

The voice echoed in the battlefield, attracting numerous gazes.

"What? Gu Yue clan still has a trump card to deal with a Rank five?"

"Believing in it is better than nothing!""Brothers, let's go, gather with the Gu Yue clan leader!!"

They were already despairing, but now that Gu Yue Bo said it, they saw some hope.

Under the pressure of death, these former enemies united and worked together, quickly gathering into one spot.

"Gu Yue clan... hehe, you are all senior brother's descendants." On the huge crane, the white brow elderly laughed coldly, about to command the cranes to intercept, but on second thoughts, he stopped that idea.

"Why not let these people escape back, so I can finish them off together. But these are all his descendants, so in the battle later, I can use them to threaten him. But these three Rank four Gu Masters have the ability to interfere with the battle, I cannot let them stay, I shall kill them first!"

Thinking so, the white brow elderly screeched strangely, flicking his finger and sending three balls of light flying.

"What Gu is this?" Xiong clan leader was first hit by the white ball, and after getting covered by it, his speed fell drastically, slower than a snail.

The other two clan leaders were the same."Fang Yuan, quickly go, Gu Yue clansmen listen up, you have to protect Fang Yuan at all costs, he's the only one that knows the method!" Gu Yue Bo tried all ways but could not get rid of this light ring, thus he screamed loudly and turned around to face the white brow elderly.

Fang Yuan turned around, looking at this Gu Yue clan leader deeply.

"Elder Fang Yuan, let us protect you!" A large number of Gu Yue clansmen gathered beside Fang Yuan, protecting him in all directions.

Healing light as well as speed buffs were all casted on Fang Yuan.

Collision sounds were heard from the back, and under the mystical and cruel fate, the three clan leaders who hated each other worked together tightly right now, battling against the mysterious elderly with their life on the line.The results of this battle, was decided from the start.

The three clan leaders died one by one as the white brow elderly flicked his sleeves, sitting firmly on the huge crane. Flying cranes engulfed the skies as they gradually forced their way into Gu Yue village.

Gu Yue village was in chaos, and the sad cries of people were heard everywhere.

Large numbers of bamboo buildings fell, and the debris area was full of corpses with white cloths covering over them. Injured members cried in pain, lying on the ground as many healing Gu Masters worked to the bone.The clan main pavilion was half devastated, and the village square was covered in a layer of blood water; this was extremely horrifying to the clansmen.

Because Tie Xue Leng and First gen Gu Yue engaged in fierce combat, it caused the mountains to shake. Thus, Gu Yue village which was right above was greatly affected.Gu Yue Yao Ji who was staying in the village, did not manage to receive Gu Yue Bo, but instead saw the injured remnants of the three clans.

"What is going on?" She shouted loudly.

Fang Yuan didn't reply, because the flock of cranes behind her was the best explanation.

"This?!" "Oh my god..."

"Is our Gu Yue clan going to perish today?"

Immediately, the village fell into chaos once again.

"Senior brother, your junior, I have come here all the way to see you. Why aren't you coming out to meet me?" White-brow elderly stood on the crane's back, his tone full of icy killing intent.

Before he was finished, on the village square, blood water gushed out like a ten metre fountain, and the bright red coffin appeared vertically.

As a blood wight, First gen Gu Yue stood inside the coffin, his blood red eyes staring closely at the white-brow elderly.

"To think that you didn't die... how did you find this place? As expected, that Gu Master earlier was instigated by you!" First gen Gu Yue said hatefully.

Chapter 192: Raising Eyebrows & Exhale

"How did I find you? Hahaha!" The white-brow elderly laughed loudly, his voice sound extremely happy, while his gaze was ruthless. He opened his palm, revealing a Gu.

It was the Kinship Bloodworm.

Kinship Bloodworm was crystal clear, like a red agate. It was like a cicada, emitting light at times, pointing towards First gen Gu Yue.

"Although senior brother stole my opportunity and backstabbed me, taking away my Gu, I still managed to learn the secret arts. Thus I refined this Kinship Bloodworm. You know how I refined it? Hehehe, using the heart blood of your two blood-related sons. They were only five to six years old and were too young, so without sufficient heart blood, I could only turn them both into living sources, taking their blood every month. After spending tens of years, I finally accumulated enough heart blood and refined this Gu." The white-brow elderly said briskly, his tone extremely smug.

"Oh, right, both your sons died soon after. HAHAHA, after refining the Kinship Bloodworm, I used it to find you for many years. But this world is too big, and you were nowhere to be found. Even though the Kinship Bloodworm was Rank five, its range is still limited. Eventually, when I was almost dying, I could only use the life-retaining Jade Burial Gu, living through death and sealing myself. Not long before this, I had to come out of sealing and I tried one last time. To think I found you by coincidence! Senior brother, do you know how happy and excited I was at that time?!"

"As for that Tie Xue Leng, hehehe, I did send him a letter to attract him here. Seeing him, I thought of our former relationship. How nostalgic. Back then we were from the same sect, chasing after demonic cultivators. We were called the Righteous Twin Cranes, having unlimited glory and pride," The white-brow elderly saying so, showed a nostalgic expression.

His expression was calm and his tone was gentle, but the more he thought about it, the stronger the killing intent was in both of his cold eyes.

This white-brow elderly, came from the Middle Continent; he was known as Lord Sky Crane.

Back then, he used the Rank five Crane Enslavement Gu and ruled over a myriad beast king level crane king and rose to fame. Because he could enslave a myriad beast king, it meant he controlled a ten thousand beast army.

This strength allowed him to use his own power and eliminate a single village.

Lord Sky Crane and First gen Gu Yue both came from the Middle Continent's Immortal Crane Sect. Hundreds of years ago, they were senior and junior brothers, closer than real brothers, killing many demonic Gu Masters and working together, having perfect synergy with each other.

In one of their attempts in chasing after demonic cultivators, they found an inheritance ground.

This inheritance was one of the many set up by the Blood Sea Ancestor. But if it was an ordinary inheritance, so be it, they would not have turned on each other.

However, this inheritance ground's treasure was beyond precious; it could allow one to rise to the heavens and become an immortal from a mortal! Thus, the two brothers were moved.

Legend says, Blood Sea Ancestor left behind over a hundred thousand inheritances, spread throughout the world. But his real motive was the few true treasures hidden in a few of these spots. They hid his personal Gu worms, his true methods.

The sect brothers encountered the Blood Sea Ancestor's true treasure inheritance.

Lord Sky Crane was quicker and obtained the inheritance. Corrupted by greed, First gen Gu Yue schemed against him and stole the Gu worm. Then he attempted to kill Lord Sky Crane, but did not succeed as the latter managed to escape.

Seeing that the matter was exposed, First gen Gu Yue could only hide his name and escape everywhere, preventing himself from getting found by his former sect. After tens of years, he could not find a Lifespan Gu, thus in his final days he stood at Qing Mao Mountain in the Southern Border, changing his appearance and calling himself Gu Yue, establishing the Gu Yue village.

Lord Sky Crane being unable to find him, was filled with hatred. Meanwhile the Immortal Crane Sect was very interested in the blood sea inheritance, thus with their help, Lord Sky Crane used the life-preserving Jade Burial Gu, falling into a deep sleep and preserving his last bit of life.

This life-preserving Jade Burial Gu's method was also a special method. Similar to First gen Gu Yue's transformation into a zombie, they were unorthodox methods and were just desperate measures.

Turning into a zombie, replacing life with death. Life-preserving life burial could enable one to hang onto life, but did not increase their lifespan.

There was only one way to increase one's lifespan in this world. Like what Fang Yuan did in his previous life, they would need to use the Lifespan Gu, increasing one's own lifespan from the roots; this was the proper way. Other methods had disadvantages and were not recognised by Heaven and Earth, belonging to helpless resorts.

"Senior brother! You shameless disciple, despicable scum! Back then when you backstabbed me, did you expect retribution today? Haha, the heavens did not let me down, for I finally found you. Today, not only will I exterminate your bloodline and destroy your thousand year plot, but I will also take back my opportunity! This day, I have waited far too long!!"

Ending his reminisces, Lord Sky Crane sighed loudly, gathering his killing intent.

But before he struck, First gen Gu Yue acted even faster!

The blood water on the ground poured up like a fountain, giving off a terrifying aura.

The sharp smell of blood spread as within the thick concentrated blood water, tens of thousands of blood guillotines flew out, tightly packed together.

Whoooosh.

Sounds of wings flapping were heard as countless bladewing blood bat Gu flew into the air, engulfing the sky and killing towards the crane flock.

The crane flock fell into chaos.

Blood guillotines and bladewing blood bats were much smaller than the Iron Beak Flying Cranes, gaining movement advantage in battle.

Lord Sky Crane was furious, screaming loudly and ordering the flying crane king he was riding on, rushing towards First gen Gu Yue.

"Retreat!" A Gu Master shouted.

The winds howled as the myriad beast king's charge was too imposing, like a meteor hitting the ground, causing people to feel shocked and afraid.

But suddenly, a blood wave flew into the sky, and the hiding blood river python assaulted under the cover of the blood water. It opened its mouth, biting at the flying crane king's long neck. At the same time its body coiled, trying to drag the flying crane king into the blood pond on the ground.

Lord Sky Crane snorted; he knew about the blood river python. Blood water was like a supreme recovery medicine for the python, thus he needed to cut the contact between them.

With this he willed in his mind, and the flying crane king stretched out its steel claws, grabbing onto the blood river python. At the same time it flapped its wings, flying towards the sky. After battling with Tie Xue Leng, the blood river python still had many injuries on its body, and its strength was also greatly diminished. Thus it was carried by the flying crane king into the air, slowing leaving the village.

"Hand over your life!" Lord Sky Crane howled, turning into a white flash and pouncing on First gen Gu Yue was who in the red coffin.

First gen Gu Yue took a step out of the coffin, and with a stretch, wings grew out of his back. These pair of wings were large and strong, like jet-black coloured bat wings.

Zombie Gu are a classic series of Gu worms, widely spread in the world. Rank two Roaming Zombie Gu, Rank three Fur Zombie Gu, Rank four Jumping Zombie Gu, Rank five Flying Zombie Gu. The Blood Wight Gu was one of the flying zombies, of course it could fly!

First gen Gu Yue's eyes burnt with raging flames as he opened his arms and showed his devious demonic claws. He spread both wings, rushing towards the sky. With a boom, he collided with Lord Sky Crane who was in the air.

The two had almost equal strength, and after retreating for a distance, they stabilized themselves and attacked once again.

Boom boom boom....

The two engaged in aerial combat, their bodies colliding constantly. The power of Rank five was fully displayed, as the aftermath of their conflicts resulted in numerous bamboo buildings collapsing.

After a while, First gen Gu Yue shouted loudly, his body covered in blood shadows, as his attacks became several times more ruthless.

Lord Sky Crane's eyes glowed with light, attacking like the slashing of a flying blade, or the piercing of an immortal sword, breaking the shadows one by one.

First gen Gu Yue breathed out a bloody mist again, prompting Lord Sky Crane to activate his Gu worm which formed a light barrier, blocking the blood mist from invading.

After a while, Lord Sky Crane was after all a dying old man, his elderly body weak, and thus his strength fell, slowly getting overpowered by First gen Gu Yue, falling into a disadvantage.

"After hundreds of years, you did not improve one bit!" First gen Gu Yue laughed loudly and mocked.

"God damn scoundrel!" Lord Sky Crane scolded in rage; he did not expect First gen Gu Yue to be so strong, be it the blood guillotine or the bladewing blood bat Gu—they were supposed to be his.

Thinking so, he got even more furious.

"Hmph, it's time to use my trump card!" Lord Sky Crane snorted secretly, his white eyebrows raising lightly, transforming.

His eyebrows grew frantically, becoming two thick bushes over tens of metres, one left and one right like snakes coming out of their dens, moving quickly and coiling around First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue struggled to no avail, his claws unceasingly attacking. These eyebrows looked fragile but were stronger than steel, and also malleable. Once restrained, it was like the roots of an old tree.

"It is actually the Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu!" First gen Gu Yue's tone changed for the first time, shocked and furious.

This Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu did not use ordinary qi, but primeval energy. Using the primeval essence in the Gu Master's aperture, and sending it out as primeval energy, this Gu was uncommon as it had a lose-lose type of usage.

By using this Gu now, not only was First gen Gu Yue's primeval essence rapidly expended, but so was Lord Sky Crane's.

Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu was like a bridge, connecting the two's aperture, causing primeval essence to be expended. It was often used by high ranking Gu Masters to bully the weak. Once used on someone stronger, it was akin to courting death.

But this situation was different.

Lord Sky Crane and First gen Gu Yue were both Rank five peak stage, but First gen Gu Yue turned into a zombie and his aperture was dead, thus he was unable to recover natural primeval essence. Although Lord Sky Crane was dying of old age and barely had any lifespan, his aperture was full of life, and his primeval essence could still recover. This attacked First gen Gu Yue's greatest weakness.

Lord Sky Crane's primeval essence was still recovering, but in First gen Gu Yue's aperture, his primeval essence would only go down and not up.

First gen Gu Yue desperately retreated, but the white eyebrows extended with him as if they were endless, and at the same time Lord Sky Crane was moving closer as well.

First gen Gu Yue howled, willing in his mind and calling the blood guillotine and bladewing blood bat Gu in attempt to cut the white eyebrows, but it had no effect. The whitebrows were extremely strong, and even if a few were cut, they would reconnect themselves.

His primeval essence continued to decrease, and if this went on, First gen Gu Yue was definitely going to lose. He was after all an ambitious man, forced to his wits end. He gritted his teeth and changed tactics, sending the blood guillotine and bladewing blood bat Gu towards Lord Sky Crane.

Lord Sky Crane had to constantly sustain the Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu, and by being attacked like this, he could only use the light barrier and defend himself passively.

The white barrier wavered and Lord Sky Crane's heart sank, the situation was not looking good for him.

Most likely, before he finishes expending First gen Gu Yue's primeval essence, his light barrier would be broken through and he would get killed by First gen Gu Yue!

Note: I am so sorry if the name "Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu" is dumb but there's no other way to translate it... Lol.

Chapter 193: Divine investigator’s last move

The Sky Crane Lord's face turned malevolent and his two eyes glinted with ominous light as he suddenly threw down a rain of feather arrows.

This arrow rain was not targetted at the First gen Gu Yue; First gen Gu Yue had already turned into a blood wight zombie, a being that possessed astounding defence and would be difficult to breach.

The feather arrows rained down and instead pierced through countless of Gu Masters, instantly killing them!

Along with this, two white lights burst out from Sky Crane Lords's eyes. As two beams of light swept through the village, wherever they went the bamboo buildings would collapse and street pavements were disintegrated. Anyone that touched these beams of light would melt like the snow meeting the sunlight.

When a Rank five Gu Master acts, he could instantly create huge casualties with every move.

Miserable shouts, screams and cries of despair continuously rang in the battlefield like a medley.

A feather arrow flower towards Fang Yuan, but he casually grabbed someone beside him and threw the man into the arrow's path. The feather arrow pierced this person's head and stopped. Fang Yuan then rolled, dodging a claw attack of an Ironbeak Flying Crane.

There was very little that a Rank three could do against a Rank five. Even Bai Ning Bing was dodging nonstop at this moment. Every time he was injured, the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique would heal him, but this also brought him closer to death itself.

Rank five Gu Masters were already at the peak of the secular world.

"Stop!" The First gen Gu Yue shouted. As he watched the Gu Masters before him getting slaughtered, his heart felt like it was bleeding.

He had a great conspiracy for establishing the village and spreading his bloodline; it was not simply just to hide his identity. The clan members were the fruits of centuries of planning. But now, as they were slaughtered by the Sky Crane Lord, it was akin to using up the First gen Gu Yue's centuries' worth of heart blood.

Being left with no choice, First gen Gu Yue could only five up on Sky Crane Lord. He ordered the blade wing blood bat Gu and blood guillotine to fly towards the village, defending it against the Sky Crane Lord's attacks.

The Sky Crane Lord laughed loudly. The Blood Sea Inheritance was focused on attack and not defence—by doing this the First gen Gu Yue was giving up on his own advantage and using his weak point to battle.

The Sky Crane Lord understood the First gen Gu Yue very well and knew his scheme. Thus he intentionally let these Gu Yue clan members go first, and then attacked them at this moment. Sure enough, he was able to escape from the perilous situation he was under while the First gen Fu Yue was troubled by trying to take care of the entire situation.

"Not good!"

As the situation continued to be in a deadlock, the First gen Gu Yue suddenly shouted. Shadows of iron chains had suddenly appeared around his entire body.

These shadows immediately turned from virtual into reality, and formed into long iron chains. These chains were like snakes and pythons as they coiled around First gen Gu Yue, binding his hands and feet.

A talisman paper also gradually appeared and stuck right between the First gen Gu Yue's eyes.

Bang.

First gen Gu Yue was bound by the iron chains; he could no longer stretch his wings and thus he fell smashing down onto the ground.

Such an unexpected scene not only shocked the First gen Gu Yue, but it also caused Sky Crane Lord to be shocked for a while before the latter started to laugh madly. "So this is the Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu and the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu. Hahaha, I guess that so-called Divine Investigator wasn't a good-for-nothing after all. My good senior brother, you are sure to die today!"

These two great Gu were both the main Gu worms of the Tie family.

The Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu could restrict a Gu Master's movement ability and thus let others trample upon them. The Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu was able to extract Gu worms from inside the Gu Master and seal them away.

Countless numbers of demonic path Gu Masters had been captured by Tie Xue Leng through these two Gu, and now he had used it on the First gen Gu Yue.

"When did this happen?!" The First gen Gu Yue was startled and also furious. He though back to the final scene when he had struck Tie Xue Leng dead.

The copper mask had flown away, revealing a square face.

Although his death was certain, there was no fear on his features. Two eyes shone with the vicissitudes of time and resoluteness as his bloodied palm struck lightly against First gen Gu Yue's chest.

However, the strength it contained was so minuscule that First gen Gu Yue had completely ignored it at the time.

"So it was then! Damn it, I would have already sensed it if I had a living body. But though my zombie body is strong in both offence and defence, it is not sensitive." The First gen Gu Yue's head was full of regrets.

There were many shortcomings when turning one's body into a blood wight. He should have already died according to his original lifespan, but he lived on by defying the heavens, so how could there not be any price to pay?

"Hahaha! The Sky Crane Lord's aura grew with his laughter, then he charged towards the First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue could only try to resist. Naturally, he fell into an absolute disadvantage.

The Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu not only bound his whole body, but the phantom image of the black iron chain also appeared within his aperture and sealed it.

The Primeval Sea surged like boiling water and many Gu worms flew around in the aperture, resisting the suppression of the Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu.

With this, the First gen Gu Yue's primeval essence expenditure became extremely huge.

"Your defeat is certain, accept your death!" Sky Crane Lord's attacks came nonstop, like he had fallen into madness.

First gen Gu Yue's head was riddled with injuries, while his pale ribs were exposed and his two arms severed from the shoulders by the Sky Crane Lord.

When it seemed that Sky Crane Lord was going to really kill him, the First gen Gu Yue suddenly opened his mouth and gave an unearthly cry.

"Yannngggg—!"

Extremely ear-piercing sound waves concentrated and instantly struck the Sky Crane Lord.

When Sky Crane Lord heard this sound, he felt like he had just met with an enormous attack, and he was sent flying dozens of steps away, his white eyebrows even pulled tight and straight. After that, he rapidly fell down to the ground.

Blood started flowing out of his eyes, nose, ears and mouth. The lingering sound was causing chaos inside his body, causing the blood to flow in reverse; he couldn't move at all for a moment.

Seeing this chance, many Gu Masters threw moon blades, water bullets and so on from a distance, but they were all blocked by the light halo on the Sky Crane Lord.

Dozens of flying cranes swarmed at the First gen Gu Yue, but their iron beaks felt like it was smashing against steel skin and iron bones as they attacked the blood wight zombie body, and broke off one after another.

A Rank five Gu's defense was no small thing. Even if Fang Yuan used the Chainsaw Golden Centipede to saw at the blood wight zombie body for some time, he might not be able to cut off even a piece of skin.

Right now, in this battle, only these two Rank five Gu Masters could threaten each other.

Although they were in a very bad state, as long as their primeval essence didn't end, others could only look on helplessly.

Sky Crane Lord saw that the flying cranes were unable to accomplish anything, while the flying crane king was fighting with the blood river python far away. As for himself, he was unable to move anything other than his eyes properly due to his qi and blood being in conflict. He concentrated his mind on the Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu, greatly accelerating the primeval essence consumption.

First gen Gu Yue was on the verge of death!

The primeval essence in his Primeval Sea quickly decreased and once it was completely used up, his Gu worms would have no primeval essence to resist the suppression of the Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu. Once this happened, Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu would start extracting the Gu worms and sealing them. That would truly be the end!

First gen Gu Yue shouted in panic, "Quick, lend me a hand! Grab the eyebrows and activate your primeval essence."

"Let's help!""Help the first ancestor!!""Let's go."

A large group of Gu Masters went to help—not only from Gu Yue clan, but even Bai and Xiong clan.

Even First gen Gu Yue was not able to cut apart these white eyebrows, so there was no way these Gu Masters' methods would work. They could only do as First gen Gu Yue said, stretching their hands and grabbing the white eyebrows.

They had just touched the white eyebrows, when some of the eyebrows split up and coiled around their wrists, arms and then finally extended to their bodies.

"Ahh....." Miserable shrieks echoed in succession.

How could a rank two Gu Master's primeval essence fight against a Rank five primeval essence? In a short while, their primeval essence was consumed clean, their Primeval Sea was empty, their apertures completely dried up; their apertures started to crack, before finally crumbling and collapsing.

The aperture was the most vital part in a human body, even more important than heart. Once the aperture broke, many Gu Masters' eyes would roll and lose their lives on the spot.

"Fuck!" First gen Gu Yue cursed in anger. The Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu was tightening up, piercing into the skin and flesh; the bones were starting to make cackling sounds.

It was reasonable to say that with Tie Xue Leng's death, this Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu couldn't get primeval essence from its Gu Master and shouldn't have been able to activate. However, it had been infected by the berserk blood Gu, and thus it could absorb the primeval essence in the air. Also, Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu was Tie Xue Leng's Gu, so it contained Tie Xue Leng's will to subdue First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue's primeval essence was depleting quickly, and he would not be able to bear it much longer.

Many Gu Masters that were rushing to provide assistance, saw this and couldn't help but slow down.

"What are you afraid of? If the first ancestor loses, we will also die! Are you hoping that you will be spared?" Fang Yuan shouted; he hurried to the side of First gen Gu Yue and grabbed the white eyebrows.

The Thousand Li Earthwolf spider had already died, and the enemy had flying cranes that could fly around to pursue and attack. There was no hope for him if he tried to escape alone.

On the contrary, if he helped First gen Gu Yue and the two sides fought each other to death, he might be able to reap some benefits.

The white eyebrows firmly locked onto Fang Yuan's wrists, then it followed to his arms and creeped along like a vine towards his waist. The snow silver primeval essence in his aperture was being quickly consumed, but Fang Yuan clenched his teeth and persevered.

His actions served as an example. Other Gu Masters were spurred and rushed forth in succession.

"Let's do this together, we might have a chance at life!""That's right, there is strength in numbers!!""Sigh, what else can we do, we can only stake our lives."

Countless hands touched the white eyebrows; Gu Masters kept on dying and many other Gu Masters kept on filling the gaps to add in to the consumption.

"Hahaha, fighting against a Rank five, how brilliant and interesting!" Bai Ning Bing also stepped forward.

"Life or death will be decided by this." Xiong Jiao Man similarly stood up.

Fang Zheng was nowhere to be seen; he was lost in the wild and hadn't escaped back to the village. Whether he lived or had died, no one could be sure, but everything bode ill for him.

Time seemed to be passing very slowly at this moment, becoming unendurable.

As time passed, many Gu Masters died. Some Gu Masters directly attacked Sky Crane Lord, but the white halo around him stood as steady as Mt. Tai.

Only Rank three Gu Masters could hold their grounds in this consumption face off.Many Gu Masters' confidence started shaking and they were beginning to hesitate.

Both sides were locked up in deadlock. Sky Crane Lord smiled grimly and said, "My victory is certain, you will all die!"

There was too big a gap between Rank three and Rank five. Rank fours would have been able to affect the situation, but the three Rank four clan leaders were already killed by Sky Crane Lord.

First gen Gu Yue was bound by the iron chains while the white eyebrows had also coiled up around him and the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu on his forehead was swaying; there was already very few primeval essence left in his aperture.

Suddenly the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu let out a faint yellow light and slowly extracted a ball of yellow light from First gen Gu Yue's aperture.

This yellow light was bigger than a fist but smaller than a basin. It slowly floated down on the ground, and only a faint glimmer of the yellow light remained.

A Gu that looked like a crystal skull showed up. The Gu was like a skull of a child that could fit on a palm, and the skull was like a crystal filled with reddish bloodstripes.

"Blood Skull Gu! After hundreds of years, I finally get to see you again!" Sky Crane Lord looked on from a distance and wept tears of joy; he was extremely moved.

Note: 'Problem Nipped in the Bud' Gu—The name of this Gu is an idiom that means: Solving the problem from the roots itself.

Chapter 194: Blood Curtain Skyflower

First gen Gu Yue clenched his bloody fangs so hard that it made cracking sounds, but he couldn't even budge, much less struggle.

Suddenly, another ball of light was captured by the yellow talisman and it fell to the ground, turning into an alternating black and white Taiji light sphere.

Two peculiar Gu worms were circling and chasing each other within this light sphere. As the Taiji light sphere continued to rotate, they seemed to carry traces of great dao, shocking many Gu Masters.

"What Gu is this?" Bai Ning Bing and many others were bewildered.

"It actually is a Rank four...." Fang Yuan's eyes focused in concentration.

"Yin Yang Rotation Gu!!" Sky Crane Lord screamed, his face clearly revealing his shock. He remained stunned for a while, then he raised his head and laughed, "My good senior brother, I truly have to thank you for finding such a good Gu. Hahaha, you actually wanted to turn back into a human, but what a pity, for your plan has been destroyed by me!"

First gen Gu Yue anxiously moved his legs and snarled; he had completely lost his manners. Whether it was Blood Skull Gu or Yin Yang Rotation Gu, they were both crucial to his plan that stretched through a millennium. Now, they were both sealed and extracted; all his painstaking plotting had almost gone in up into smoke now.

Sky Crane Lord's smile turned even more jubilant, his desire for vengeance was fully satisfied by seeing this expression of First gen Gu Yue.

Another yellow light that was captured fell to the ground; it was a scarlet colored Gu and looked like a translucent water sphere.

On seeing this Gu, First gen Gu Yue suddenly stopped his struggle; he was exulted. He opened his bloody mouth, revealing his fangs as he shouted, "Quick, destroy this Gu worm!"

Several Gu Masters immediately moved forward upon hearing this and used their attacks.

This Gu had been sealed by Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu, stopping the First gen Gu Yue from activating it with his thoughts. There was a layer of yellow light on the surface carrying an imprint; it could only be unsealed by Tie Xue Leng or by using some special Gu worms.

However, this Gu was an expendable Gu and was special as it needed to be destroyed to be activated.

Several Gu Masters made their moves; the yellow light imprint was only a sealing Gu worm and didn't have any defensive powers. After several attacks, the yellow light imprint collapsed, destroying the sealed Gu worm along with it.

Buzz!

A soft cry resounded, and a blood light bloomed, suddenly expanding and turning into a spherical shield within moments.

First gen Gu Yue was within the shield, while Sky Crane Lord was outside.

The blood red shield's range was six mu, and Bai Ning Bing and Fang Yuan were both within the shield, whereas Xiong Jiao Man and some others were outside.

The most encouraging part was that the white eyebrows were instantly cut apart into two halves by this shield; with the disintegration of the white eyebrows, Fang Yuan and others recovered control of their bodies.

"The aura of this shield reaches Rank five, but why does it resemble the Water Curtain Skyflower Gu?" Fang Yuan was bewildered; he had never seen this Gu before.

Sky Crane Lord was separated by this shield, and he staggered up before laughing coldly, "Senior brother, such a good move, you are actually able to counterattack and break my Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu. It's a pity such a trifle defense won't work against me, you are just prolonging your imminent defeat by doing this!"

First gen Gu Yue instead laughed loudly, "Junior brother, how about testing it yourself?"

"That's my intention!" Killing intent flashed in Sky Crane Lord's eyes; countless flying cranes and feather arrows shot towards the shield, while his eyes also sent out the white beams at the same time.

However, the blood shield was still unshakeable and was as stable as before.

Sky Crane Lord's face turned extremely dark as he stopped his attacks, "What Gu is this?"

Gu Yue first threw his head back and laughed, "Let me teach you, this is my personally fused gu: Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu. The Water Curtain Skyflower Gu—a Rank four gu—can block Rank five Gu attacks. This Gu is at Rank five and has even more powerful defense. Water Curtain Skyflower Gu prevents its owner from going in and out; but this Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu lets me go out. Junior brother, don't be impatient, you can attack slowly, use all your strength. Just wait till I recover, then I'll come out and cut your dog head, ahhaha!"

"You thief, keep on boasting!" Sky Crane Lord was in turmoil; he had everything in his grasp before, but to think First gen Gu Yue was able to recover some ground and the situation turned into a deadlock again.

He attacked madly and extremely fiercely, killing all the Gu Masters outside the shield including Xiong Jiao Man.

However, inside the Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu, all was calm and quiet. The blood shield was as stable as Mt. Tai, and the group of Gu Masters inside the shield were relieved.

"First ancestor is indeed an unrivalled hero!"

"We are finally saved. The first ancestor will show his divine might and this person will definitely be defeated."

"Hu, this is the strength of Rank five Gu Master? I am actually still alive in front of such strength!"

The Gu Masters cheered and shouted.

On the contrary, Bai Ning Bing snorted; his death was certain due to the Ten extreme aptitude, but this deadlock decreased the splendor of it and he was not happy about it.

Sky Crane Lord kept on attacking for a long while with no results. At one moment, he suddenly stopped as if he had woken up.

First gen Gu Yue's words were meant to incite him into attacking the Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu and wasting his primeval essence. If he wasn't wrong, this Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu had the same effect as Water Curtain Skyflower Gu. Its fusion price was extremely high and belonged to one time use expendable category, but it had a high defense, albeit with a set duration. It would automatically dissipate after a certain amount of time.

At this thought, Sky Crane Lord sat cross-legged, then took out two primeval stones and pinched them, starting to recover his primeval essence.

"Lend me a hand, you will only have a chance at life by helping me. Primeval stones, I need a large number of them!" First gen Gu Yue shouted—the surrounding Gu Masters immediately took out primeval stones and piled them around him.

First gen Gu Yue opened his bloody mouth wide and breathed in deeply, sucking the primeval stones into his mouth.

Crack, he chewed the primeval stones; large amounts of natural primeval essence poured into his aperture.

On seeing this, the Sky Crane Lord became anxious and started shouting, "Don't give them to him, you morons! Once he recovers his movement, he will kill you all and use your blood to upgrade his aptitude. You are causing your own doom!"

"Hmph, using such a low level tactic to sow distrust, so ridiculous!"

"Quick, this old thief is telling us not to give it, so we need to give even more primeval stones."

"Everything depends on lord ancestor!"

Gu Masters provided the primeval stones generously and soon, great quantities of primeval stones entered First gen Gu Yue's mouth. Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing watched indifferently from the side.

A normal body wouldn't be able to endure such a large amount of primeval essence pouring into them, but First gen Gu Yue's blood wight zombie body was powerful and strong. The primeval essence in his Primeval Sea began to rise rapidly.

The Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu was becoming weaker, and after quite a while, it turned into a pool of blood; it had thoroughly died out.

With the bindings gone, First gen Gu Yue gave a long roar and activated his blood wight vital Gu. Great quantities of blood were absorbed into his body, and within moments, his powerful arms grew back again with claws as sharp as a knife.

He gave a hearty laugh then stood up.

At this exact moment, the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu on his forehead also turned into a pool of blood and completely dissipated.

"It seems the heavens do not want me dead!" First gen Gu Yue threw his head back and laughed.

"We ask first ancestor to behead this old thief!"

"Once the lord ancestor makes his move, he will definitely succeed."

The group of Gu Masters was elated.

First gen Gu Yue's laughter gradually stopped, and fire burned in his eyes as he spoke unhurriedly, "I will, of course, kill my enemy. But before killing him, I still have something I need to do."

"Not good." Fang Yuan's heart suddenly jumped when he heard the tone of the voice, and he discreetly moved towards the outer edge of the group.

The people beside him were puzzled by this but they were still filled with high fighting spirit, "We are not sure what first ancestor has to do, but we will serve the ancestor to the best of our abilities!"

First gen Gu Yue threw his head back and cackled with laughter, "Haha, the thing I need to do is to take your lives!"

"What?!" The crowd turned pale with shock.

First gen Gu Yue, however, didn't hesitate to make his move.

Squelch, his claw immediately pierced through a Rank three Gu Master near him. When he took back his palm, there was a pulsing heart on it.

This Gu Master was a Gu Yue clan member, and his expression was one of disbelief at this moment. He gave a loud scream, blood spurting out like a fountain as he fell down with his head facing up.

"Good blood, it can't be wasted," First gen Gu Yue exclaimed. With a shift of his mind, the Blood Skull Gu flew up and made one round around this Gu Master's body.

The Gu Master's corpse twitched, and all the blood in him was extracted by the Blood Skull Gu, entering into its two empty eye sockets.

After the Blood Skull Gu drank its fill, the blood stripes on its crystal skull turned even brighter.

"First ancestor, you?!" As the group retreated with all their might, someone cried out.

"Noisy!" First gen Gu Yue's figure flashed and appeared in front of this person, slashing his body into two with a knife. Blood spurted out and was absorbed by the Blood Skull Gu.

"First ancestor, you ungrateful beast, if not for our primeval stones, how could you have any fighting strength left?!"

"This first ancestor is no decent person, everyone lets attack together and kill him!"

"That's right, there is power in numbers....ahh!"

A bloody massacre unfolded. First gen Gu Yue was a peak Rank five and he had completely recovered his primeval essence. These Gu Masters were just Rank one, Rank two or at most Rank three, so how could they be his match?

And this Blood Curtain Skyflower separated inside from outside, forming a sealed space. Only its master, First gen Gu Yue could go out. But once he exited, he couldn't enter again; he would have to destroy the Blood Curtain Skyflower or wait for it to dissipate.

The group of Gu Masters weren't able to escape, they tried fighting but were utterly defeated and killed by First gen Gu Yue.

Except for Bai clan's and Xiong clan's Gu Masters, he killed every Gu Yue clansmen and used the Blood Skull Gu to absorb the blood. After killing several hundreds, the Rank four Blood Skull Gu was glistening red, as it had reached the limit of what it could absorb.

First gen Gu Yue laughed loudly and summoned the Blood Skull Gu; the Blood Skull Gu came towards him and floated above his head.

"This day, this moment, my centuries of arduous planning has finally come to fruition!" He let out a long exhalation of relief. At this moment, the Blood Skull Gu opened its tightly shut mouth and threw up a blood fountain.

The blood fountain didn't have the fishy odor of blood, but instead let out a sweet relaxing fragrance.

This blood fountain poured from above First gen Gu Yue and completely soaked him.

However, what was strange and mysterious was that not even a drop of the blood fountain sprayed on the ground. All of the blood stuck to First gen Gu Yue's body, then slowly seeped inside, finally reaching the aperture.

First gen Gu Yue stood on the spot; he was silent and his head was down as he appreciated this moment. Suddenly, he burst out with a crazed laughter as he spoke, "Kakakaka, my aptitude has advanced, my aptitude has really advanced!"

The rest of the Gu Masters tremored.

Outside the blood shield, Sky Crane Lord pointed at First gen Gu Yue and furiously shouted, "Return my Blood Skull Gu back to me!"

Chapter 195: Then let me become a demon

First gen Gu Yue laughed with even more joy; suddenly, he stopped laughing and turned towards Lord Sky Crane, speaking with a voice filled with hatred, "Junior brother, you never thought there would be a day like this, right?! We were both orphans raised by the master. But since young, master always pampered you more. Why? Isn't it because your aptitude is A grade and mine is only C grade?"

"Naturally, with your A grade aptitude, your cultivation progressed much faster. Did you know, with my C grade aptitude, how much sweat and effort I had to put in compared to you, just barely be able to match with your pace? Although we were called the Twin Cranes of Righteous Paths—you were always the main and I the second. You were like the brightest star, just because you were an A grade genius!"

"Even your luck was good and you obtained one of the true inheritances of Blood Sea ancestor. Blood Skull Gu could purify the blood of the relatives killed and pour them into the aperture, upgrading it. Did you know what my mood was like at the time? I thought day and night, thinking of countless schemes. I knew the Blood Skull Gu was my only hope; with it, I could change my life, change my fate!"

"But it is mine, MINE!" Lord Sky Crane was so angry that he stamped his feet repeatedly.

"Yes, it is yours." First gen Gu Yue nodded, "Your aptitude is great and your luck is also great. Clearly, we started out at the same time, killing enemies together, but the heavens only appreciated you, giving you the true inheritance. Did you know, when I looked at your proud expression and listened to you talking about your future plans, when I was forcing myself to smile, I suddenly realized."

"The heavens favored you, gave you A grade aptitude and the true blood sea inheritance. But what could I do about it? I was only an insignificant C grade talent, so how could I succeed just by relying on myself? I could only seize, rob! Change what wasn't mine to become mine! The fate that heaven had planned for me was to let me bow under someone, making me a shadow behind others! But I am indignant, for on what basis did he put me below and you above?" First gen Gu Yue actually seemed to be weeping and whimpering at the end.

Blood wight zombie's appearance was extremely terrifying, and adding on to this strange sound, anyone who heard it would feel coldness seep into their bones.

"Since the heavens don't favor me, master doesn't love me, other people don't value me—I can only love myself more, I can only value myself more, I can only rely on myself more. I can only put in more effort, I can only take more risks, I can only exert myself more! Only then can I succeed! But the righteous path talks of moral codes, ethics, comradeship, qualifications, hierarchy. I am only a lone person, a nobody with no background, no talent and no resources. So tell me, how could I succeed?"

"With the righteous path, I could only let myself be exploited and bullied, I could only look up to these Young Masters and geniuses. Even if I kept on increasing my qualifications until I got old, I would only achieve minute success. This is the righteous path... a bullshit path!"

"Only by becoming a demon, forsaking ethics, comradeship, the social rules and paying a huge price, I could take another path among the thorns and brambles, a path that belonged to myself! So, I schemed against you, seized your blood sea true inheritance and became a demon. Haha, and a demon I became!"

A demon I became...

A demon I became...

The voice reverberated within the blood shield.

Outside the shield, Lord Sky Crane was in a quiet and sombre mood.

First gen Gu Yue slowly stopped laughing then began killing again. Large numbers of Gu Masters were killed, their blood absorbed by the Blood Skull Gu and concentrated into the blood fountain, pouring into First gen Gu Yue's aperture and raising his aptitude.

The higher the aptitude, the more primeval essence could be stored in the aperture.

As First gen Gu Yue killed more and more Gu Yue clansmen, his aptitude kept on increasing. After chewing the primeval stones, his primeval essence increased and his fighting strength became more powerful.

Outside the blood shield, Lord Sky Crane was burning with anxiety, but the Blood Curtain Skyflower was like a deep chasm; he could do nothing but sigh. He had tried to prevent it, but he could only give up.

As time passed on, there were only a few numbers of people left inside the blood shield.

"Brat, you stole the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus. I will give you a chance to atone for your crime, obediently hand it over and your life will be spared!" First gen Gu Yue walked closer step by step, his killing intent firmly locking Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan knew the chance of his survival was scarce, but his expression didn't change and instead sneered, "Only three year old children might be deceived by your bullshit. Hmph, I will destroy Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus if you come any closer. You should know that I have refined this Gu and can easily cause it to self-destruct with a thought. It's up to you."

First gen Gu Yue's steps slowed, then he resolutely and quickly pressed on towards Fang Yuan.

"Brat, you have guts and you are smart too. You are indeed my descendant, I will take your blood and use it to raise my aptitude. Of course, I won't let you go. Originally, I used a blood type Gu to purify my heir's blood lineage, to try and bring out a descendant with the Ancient Moon Desolate Yin physique. As long as I absorbed the blood of such a genius, I would be able to raise my aptitude sharply to 99% A grade aptitude!"

"If it had been so, I could have let you guys go, but unfortunately your luck doesn't seem to be good. Humph, the thing I hate the most in my life is being coerced. If Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus dies then so be it, but you are sure to die!"

His words hadn't even finished when the two wings on his back flapped, propelling him forward; in the blink of an eye, he appeared in front of Fang Yuan.

First gen Gu Yue made a grabbing motion with his right hand; in that split second, Fang Yuan's pupils shrunk, and his hairs stood on the end as he retreated hastily.

However, how could it be easy to dodge a Rank five expert? The blood wight claws were almost upon him, but suddenly an ice hand pierced in from his side.

BANG.

There was the sound of a collision, and the ice hand shattered and cold aura flew all over the place; the First gen Gu Yue had to take a step back.

"Bai Ning Bing?!" Fang Yuan was shocked when he turned around to look at the person who had helped him.

Bai Ning Bing took back his broken arm, and cold air blew out from the wound and instantly condensed into a new ice hand just like before. It was just that there was no flesh in the hand—he was already reaching the lifespan limits of his ten extreme aptitude.

"To think that I can have a such a splendid death. It's a pity I won't be able to see the conclusion to this battle!" Bai Ning Bing heaved a deep sigh, then suddenly smiled and looked at Fang Yuan with his deep blue pupils, "Fang Yuan, you and I are the same kind of people. My death is certain, but it would be a real pity if you were to die too. So I will protect you, but I have a condition."

Bai Ning Bing may only be a Rank three Gu Master, but as his death closed upon him, his fighting strength continued to grow steeply like a water fountain. The final hope to win against First gen Gu Yue was him!

"What condition?" Fang Yuan's gaze flashed.

Bai Ning Bing stretched out his two arms like he was embracing the world. Clothed in a white gown, matching with his snowy white hair and sharp eyebrows, he said, "Live on for me and witness the myriad wonders of this world!"

In that moment, Fang Yuan was emotionally moved!

This man...

Fang Yuan looked at Bai Ning Bing and he felt like he was looking at his younger self in his previous life.

Bai Ning Bing's words might sound like nonsense, but they were genuine. Maybe, ordinary people would never believe it, but Fang Yuan understood the profound meaning contained within these words.

Bai Ning Bing was a top genius, his talent in defiance of the heavens and but his lifespan superficially short. He had already found his path, and found his faith. He wasn't afraid of death but he was reluctant to leave this world.

He had regrets, but under this situation where he had no other alternatives, he could only entrust them to Fang Yuan.

"Oh, it actually is Northern Dark Ice Soul physique! Tsk, such a pity that you are not a descendant of my lineage, otherwise they wouldn't have needed to die." First gen Gu Yue smiled malevolently. "But you want to block me by relying on this Northern Dark Ice Soul physique? So naive!"

His figure disappeared and appeared right in front of Bai Ning Bing.

BOOM!

There was a noise of explosion, and the two had traded off a blow.

First gen Gu Yue was forced back two steps whereas Bai Ning Bing's whole skull and most of his body was blown away.

But in the next instant, crackle, crack...

Cold air permeated the area, ice and frost condensed together to again grow out the body and the skull—Bai Ning Bing was resurrected!

"What!" First gen Gu Yue got the shock of his life. Ten extreme aptitudes were rarely seen and this was the first time he was facing one.

Two people traded off blows again. In the end, Bai Ning Bing's cultivation level was weak and was firmly pressed in a disadvantageous position, so the situation looked very bad. However, no matter how First gen Gu Yue killed him, he didn't die.

At this moment, Bai Ning Bing's Northern Dark Ice Soul body was close to an undying body; no matter how severe the wounds, they would be frozen back to the original state in a matter of seconds.

Gu Yue Bo was becoming more furious and also fearful, and he crazily increased his offensive attacks. Bai Ning Bing gradually lost all color of life, turning into a moving iceman. Even his white hair had turned into thin icicles.

The time had finally arrived...

Death was descending at this moment.

"Infinite brilliance in the mortal realm, to the ends of the world the skies and seas stretch beyond. As the winds blow my ashes back to the earth, it is incomparable to the shining moon in the reflection of the water!" Bai Ning Bing recited a poem with a faint smile.

Henceforth, his facial expression froze.

There was a burst of cold wind and the fog like frost suddenly rose up.

Crackle.....

Large amounts of ice started spreading from under his feet, then the glacier rose up like the birth of a mountain!

The surging majestic ice was like a landslide, like a tsunami, like a dragon rolling on the waves, as it crushed towards First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue let out a gasp and brought out all his strength to resist it. The red hairs on his head were all standing on end, mist of blood rising from all over his body, and large numbers of blood guillotine and bladewing blood bat Gu were sent to crash against the glacier in an attempt to slow it down even by a bit.

In the end, he was still suppressed by the glacier, confined and engulfed.

The enormous glacier filled the whole blood shield, but it didn't touch Fang Yuan as he was in a small space left intentionally by Bai Ning Bing.

Bang.

The Blood Curtain Skyflower burst with a soft sound. With no hindrances, the cold air crazily flew around, and ice immediately condensed into a glacier which continued to spread.

"It broke the shield of Blood Curtain Skyflower gu! Such power..." Lord Sky Crane didn't dare face the glacier as he promptly took to the air.

Under his astonished gaze, the glacier continued to spread and actually covered the whole Qing Mao mountain from the top of the mountain to the bottom. In this instance, the lush, thriving Qing Mao mountain turned into a sinister land of ice and snow.

The icy ground under Fang Yuan's feet continued to raise higher, he too was personally observing this scene.

This thousand li glacier was the evidence of the fall of a young genius, and contained within it was Bai Ning Bing's indignance and helpless sigh.

"Not good, I need leave this place soon! Bai Ning Bing's consciousness is weakening and gradually dying out, he is already losing the control of the glacier." Fang Yuan found that the space he was on was shrinking, ice continuously condensed and moved forward, compressing the space he was on.

Chapter 196: Rebirth once more

Fang Yuan immediately used the Chainsaw Golden Centipede, as well as the Blood Moon Gu, trying to break the ice.

But the ice layer was way too thick, and the coldness was oozing. Every layer of ice he shaved off, two layers would grow. Fang Yuan was trapped in a desperate situation, without any way to free himself.

At this same time, blood light emerged from under the icy river.

There was initially a hint of blood light, but it soon spread, becoming stronger and stronger, until a blood coloured aurora enveloped the area.

"Hahaha." With a long laugh, blood light rushed towards the sky as First gen Gu Yue broke the ice and escaped. Although he looked miserable, his tone was arrogant, "This Northern Dark Ice Soul physique, if he reached Rank four, he might be able to kill me. Sadly for him, he is only a Rank three peak stage..."

Saying so, he turned his gaze to Fang Yuan within the ice river.

"Northern Dark Ice Soul physique couldn't kill you, then let me do it." Far in the sky, Lord Sky Crane flew over casually. The Ironbeak flying crane king he was sitting on, had already returned after killing the blood river python when they flew away earlier.

At this point, in the entire Qing Mao mountain, only three people remained.

Bai Ning Bing had already turned into the ice mountain, his consciousness expended. Fang Yuan was like an insect inside an amber, trapped within the ice.

As for the two Rank five Gu Masters however, after First gen Gu Yue raised his aptitude, his aperture could store much more primeval essence. Lord Sky Crane had already recovered most of his strength after resting.

The two's gaze were focused on Fang Yuan.

First gen Gu Yue wanted to kill Fang Yuan, to take his blood. Lord Sky Crane wanted to stop First gen Gu Yue, and he would naturally not restrict himself by protecting Fang Yuan, thus he could only strike first and kill Fang Yuan.

With their natures, they would not tolerate a bystander. After all, what if both of them got injured, and a third person profited from it?

Fang Yuan sighed. Seeing their gazes, he knew he was finished.

He had lost the Thunderwings Gu and Thousand Li Earthwolf spider. Even if he had them, he could not escape from two Rank five Gu Masters.

He only had Rank three peak stage cultivation, incomparable with Rank five. In this situation, he was like fish meat, easily cut by knives. And these were two extremely sharp knives!

He could not beat them in combat, and couldn't escape from them either, but Fang Yuan had a final move!

That is—Spring Autumn Cicada!

Fang Yuan's mind went into his aperture. The light walls in his aperture had turned into a rough stone aperture.

His snow silver primeval essence was about half left. The stone aperture no longer had recovery abilities, but Fang Yuan's Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus maintained such a scene in his aperture.

These were not important; he placed all his concentration on the Gu in the middle.

His vital Gu, the Rank six Spring Autumn Cicada!

Only by using this Gu could he travel against the flow of time, creating a new miracle!! Using an impossible method to change fate itself!

Even then—

Such a method, was extremely risky.

The river of time is a forbidden area in the great dao, mortals are not allowed to traverse in it. Once they enter, it is breaking the rules of heaven and earth, and they would face divine retribution.

Secondly, Spring Autumn Cicada had not fully recovered, so it was like a broken boat forcefully travelling in the river of time, he might capsize mid-way and sink.

Lastly, Fang Yuan was only at Rank three peak stage. Activating the Spring Autumn Cicada now was like a baby using a sword, and he might easily get hurt by the sword.

"Once I use the Spring Autumn Cicada, I will have to self detonate. Using all my cultivation and the flesh and blood of my body, as well as all my other Gu worms, as a driving force to move the Spring Autumn Cicada forward. Compared to my previous life,even if I self detonate, this force is too small, and there is a high chance it would kill me directly. But at this point, I have no other ways left, I am forced to use this Gu!"

Fang Yuan was helpless too.

Earlier, he would rather use the Stone Aperture Gu than the Spring Autumn Cicada, because of the great risk involved.

Given 100%, there was less than even 10% chance of succeeding.

Many times, when Gu Masters use high ranking Gu, they would face a strong backlash. Like Gu Yue Qing Shu, right now Fang Yuan could only bet on the fact that "Spring Autumn Cicada is his vital Gu".

"Little rascal, hand over your life and contribute your blood to your ancestor!'

"Lad, you are unlucky, you can only blame this despicable ancestor of yours. I will set you free from your misery!"

First gen Gu Yue and Lord Sky Crane both attacked at once.

Fang Yuan was forced to the cliff's end, he could only jump.

"Spring Autumn Cicada, do it!" His eyes glowed with wondrous light, as two green and yellow lights burst forth from his body.

"This aura?!"

"How can this be? A Rank six Gu!"

At once, the two Rank five Gu Masters were shocked, but soon, greed emerged on their faces.

"Kill him and take the Rank six Gu!"

"This is a an opportunity from heaven, good lad, hand it over and I may spare your life!"

Their speed was even faster than before.

But at this time, a loud boom occurred.

Fang Yuan self detonated!

"What?!" Before his death, he heard the two Rank five Gu Master's cries of shock.

Legend says, the world has one long river, known as time! Humans were like fish in the river, and under the currents, the fish could only flow downwards. Sometimes, one or two fish would jump above the surface of the river and see the events below—this was predicting the future.

Without the river of time, the world would be still, becoming a drawing. Only with this river can change occur, and the world can move, either prospering or withering.

The river of time, with roaring currents. Every ripple was a story, an event that occured in the past.

Under the turbulent river water, a tiny Gu worm was flowing upstream.

It spread its wings, moving with difficulty. With the waves crashing against it, every impact could nearly cause its demise.

It carried Fang Yuan's consciousness and memories, while a yellow green light was protecting its body. It moved up the river shakingly, like a candle blown by the wind.

Eventually, it could only move up a little, before the yellow green light dispersed. The Spring Autumn Cicada had reached its limit, and with a swoosh, it turned into a flash and burrowed into one of the ripples.

Fang Yuan's body shook, his eyes having a tint of yellow green light deep within.

This light flashed by quickly, and Fang Yuan shuddered.

Consciousness and memories assaulted his brain, merging instantly.

He succeeded!

He was extremely happy, he had rebirthed once more!

After sensing this, he immediately looked around, observing his surroundings.

He found that his primeval essence was being expended as his arms and body were coiled by white eyebrows.

Seeing once again, oh!

So it was this moment.

Tie Xue Leng's backup plan activated already. First gen Gu Yue was trapped by iron chains, not being able to move. His forehead also had a yellow talismen, the Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu and the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu.

That Lord Sky Crane also landed on the ground, his body covered in a white barrier. He activated the Raise Eyebrows & Exhale Gu, trying to exhaust all of First gen Gu Yue's primeval essence.

Fang Yuan squinted. He was coiled by the white eyebrows, not able to move, thus he could only use up primeval essence and wait for a good chance.

Under the effect of the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu, a yellow light flew out of First gen Gu Yue's body.

This yellow light was about fist-size, smaller than a person's face. It casually landed on the ground, showing the Blood Skull Gu inside.

"Blood Skull Gu! After hundreds of years, I finally see you again!" Lord Sky Crane on seeing this, was exhilarated and his expression extremely excited.

Gu Yue first head clenched his bloody fangs so hard that it made cracking sounds, but he couldn't even budge, much less struggle.

Suddenly, another ball of light was captured by the yellow talisman and fell to the ground, turning into the alternating black and white Taiji light sphere.

Two peculiar Gu worms were circling and chasing each other within this light sphere. It was the Yin Yang Rotation Gu.

According to Fang Yuan's memories, Lord Sky Crane shouted again, "Yin Yang Rotation Gu, my good senior brother, I truly have to thank you for finding such a good Gu. Hahaha, you actually wanted to turn back to a human, but what a pity your plan was destroyed by me!"

Fang Yuan looked at First gen Gu Yue.

Indeed, he was anxiously moved his legs and snarled, he had completely lost his manners.

"Wait a bit longer, my opportunity is coming." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, choosing to wait a bit longer.

The third yellow light that was captured fell to the ground; it was a scarlet colored Gu and looked like a translucent water sphere.

Fang Yuan's heart jumped: "Blood Curtain Skyflower!"

It was this Gu that changed the situation and allowed First gen Gu Yue to overturn the crisis.

Blood Curtain Skyflower was created by First gen Gu Yue, Fang Yuan didn't know it earlier but now he was clear of its effects.

Indeed, afterwards, First gen Gu Yue shouted, "Quick someone, destroy this Gu worm!"

Several Gu Masters immediately moved forward upon hearing this and immediately used their attacks.

Swoosh!

A soft cry resounded, Blood Curtain Skyflower appeared again, the blood color sphere shield isolating the two areas. Some people were outside, while some were inside.

The blood shield broke the white eyebrows completely, and Fang Yuan and the others no longer had to compete with the Lord Sky Crane in primeval essence, thus regaining freedom.

Lord Sky Crane was blocked by this Gu, hurriedly getting up and snickering continuously.

After some conversation, he could not break the blood shield, and had to stop, asking, "What Gu is this?"

Gu Yue laughed smugly, "Let me teach you, this is my personally fused Gu—Blood Curtain Skyflower. Water Curtain Skyflower—a Rank four Gu—can block Rank five Gu attacks. This Gu is at Rank five and has even more powerful defense. Water Curtain Skyflower prevents even its owner from going in and out; but this Blood Curtain Skyflower can let me leave. Junior brother, don't be impatient, you can attack slowly, use all your strength. Just wait till I recover, I will then come out and cut away your dog head, ahahaha!"

Lord Sky Crane was furious, attacking again, but failed. After he calmed down, he chose to replenish his primeval essence, waiting for the blood shield to lose effect.

The Gu Masters seeing the blood shield being impenetrable, were overjoyed thinking their lives were saved, quickly flattering First gen Gu Yue, but only Bai Ning Bing snorted.

First gen Gu Yue thus asked for more primeval stones, and everyone quickly contributed what they had.

Although First gen Gu Yue was chained up, and could not move, his mouth continued to crush primeval stones as he recovered quickly.

Sky Crane Lord seeing this, started shouting, "You morons! Once he recovers his movement, he will kill you all and use your blood to upgrade his aptitude. You are causing your own doom!"

No one believed him.

"Hehe, using such a low level tactic to sow distrust, we'll laugh till our teeth drops!"

"Quick, this old thief is telling us not to give, so we need to give even more primeval stones."

"Everything is depending on lord ancestor!"

Chapter 197: Changing Fate!

Large numbers of primeval stones continued to be absorbed by First gen Gu Yue, as he chewed and crushed them.

Bai Ning Bing watched coldly.

But Fang Yuan moved; he did not observe but had a different choice than before.

"First gen Ancestor, the situation is dire, I have the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus to offer!" He was filled with sincerity as he walked up quickly, a look of helplessness but determination.

Gu Yue laughed heartily, "Very good, as expected of my descendant. Such filial piety, as your ancestor, I am very happy!"

He had long wanted the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, and once sent two bladewing blood bat groups to chase after Fang Yuan, but Fang Yuan escaped quickly and didn't give him the chance.

However right now he had no suspicions.

Firstly, he did not fall out with Fang Yuan yet, and earlier he had lied that he was protecting Fang Yuan when he dispatched the bladewing blood bat group.

Secondly, Fang Yuan had taken the initiative to grab onto the white eyebrows and help the First gen Gu Yue in the primeval essence expenditure, causing the wavering people to make up their minds. Such a loyal performance, First gen Gu Yue still remembered it vividly.

Lastly, under such circumstances, Fang Yuan could only place his hopes on First gen Gu Yue. Only then could he defeat Lord Sky Crane and protect his life. First gen Gu Yue did not believe that Fang Yuan would ruin his own survival chances and attack him.

Thus, when Fang Yuan got closer, First gen Gu Yue laughed continuously, "With the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, my chances of victory is higher by 20%. All of you move away, and let him in."

"Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus?" Outside the blood barrier, Lord Sky Crane was stunned and quickly shouted, "You mustn't do it!"

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Yuan got to First gen Gu Yue's side.

"First gen ancestor. I have thought it through! It was you who created the village, it was because of you that all of us descendants exist. Back in the day, you made such a great contribution to the village. Today, you even led our clan towards brilliance. The Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus should be used by you, great ancestor." He was full of admiration, his tone excited and nervous.

First gen Gu Yue nodded continuously, thinking: This lad is good with words. Too bad I still have to kill him later and retrieve his blood.

But at this time!

Fang Yuan lowered his back, striking.

He grabbed First gen Gu Yue, using the strength in his waist to turn his body and moved both arms.

He opened his mouth and growled, using the strength of two boars, expending all his energy to throw!

Swish!

First gen Gu Yue was thrown out of the blood barrier by him.

Dead silence!

At this time, it was as if time stopped.

The outside winds blew relentlessly. First gen Gu Yue was smashed onto the ground, his red hair flying around in the winds as he stared blankly, having unable to react to what had just happened.

In front of him, less than ten steps away was Lord Sky Crane.

This old man was still furious and anxious over Fang Yuan contributing the Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus. He did not expect in the least that in the very next moment, such a drastic change would occur.

He was stunned too, staring blankly at First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue was his mortal enemy, but at this point Lord Sky Crane was stunned, like he was still dreaming, not moving at all.

In the blood barrier, everyone stood like a statue, silent and unmoving.

Some people opened their mouths, so large that a fist could fit in it. Some stared with wide-opened eyes, almost bulging out.

Even Bai Ning Bing lost his composure, staring at Fang Yuan in astonishment.

Only when half a bamboo building collapsed within the blood barrier did everyone jolt awake all of a sudden.

"Wha... what... what the fuck!" Someone swore.

"Fang Yuan, what dumb shit did you do!" Someone pointed at Fang Yuan, his entire body shivering.

"First gen ancestor!!" Someone attempted to pull First gen Gu Yue back, but was blocked by the Blood Curtain Skyflower.

"Despicable thief! Lying to your ancestor, I will tear you to shreds!" First gen Gu Yue finally reacted, lying on the ground screaming.

"Hahaha..." Amidst the frightened individuals, someone laughed.

It was none other than Bai Ning Bing.

He laughed till his tears came out, giving a thumbs up to Fang Yuan, "Interesting, interesting, truly spectacular."

"Fang Yuan, are you crazy?"

"Fang Yuan, you harmed the First gen ancestor, you plot even against the ancestor, are you still human?!"

"Waaaaaah, Fang Yuan must've been bought over by that white hair old man. You spy, you traitor!!"

The surrounding people pointed at him in rage, but Fang Yuan lightly laughed, "I am a Rank three peak stage, who dares to kill me? Who can kill me?"

At this point, within the blood barrier, there were few Rank three Gu Masters. They had little primeval essence left due to the fight earlier, and they even gave up their primeval stones and could not get replenishments. As for the others, they were mortals or Rank one or two Gu Masters.

Without the First gen Gu Yue, within this blood barrier, Fang Yuan really was unstoppable.

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed, bending down and picking up the two Gu worms.

His left hand carried the Blood Skull Gu, and his right hand carried the Yin Yang Rotation Gu. These two were owned by First gen Gu Yue, but right now they had a thin layer of yellow light, sealed by the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu, unable to sense First gen Gu Yue's desperate calls.

But this seal was an obstacle to Fang Yuan as well.

He wanted to break the seal and refine the two Gu worms. Forcefully breaking the seal however, will only cause these two Gu to be destroyed.

This was different from the Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu, as the Blood Curtain Skyflower Gu had to be destroyed to be used. By breaking the seal, it was the same as using it.

But Fang Yuan was not anxious.

He knew what would happen next. Both the Demon Suppression Iron Chain Gu and Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu would be corrupted by the Blood Frenzy Gu, turn into blood water and die.

"Hahaha, my good senior brother, to think you have this day! Hand over your life!" Lord Sky Crane howled, rushing into the sky and attacking towards First gen Gu Yue.

First gen Gu Yue was suppressed by the demon suppressing chains and could not move, thus he was a target board and could only take the hits.

He scolded furiously, howling and struggling.

Suddenly the iron chains turned into a puddle of blood water, allowing him to regain his freedom and he hurriedly flew into the air, crashing against the blood barrier.

With a loud bang, unquestionably, he was blocked by the blood barrier.

This Blood Curtain Skyflower was refined by him, and it was his greatest invention. It had superb defense, but once used it cannot be moved nor turned off. For him, he could only exit and not enter.

"Little rascal, you will die a painful death!" First gen Gu Yue's grievance and rage towards Fang Yuan was greater than anything, rising like a tsunami.

Lord Sky Crane naturally chased him, laughing non-stop.

First gen Gu Yue could only give up on the blood barrier and resist the Lord Sky Crane. He had eaten large amounts of primeval essence earlier, thus he had ample primeval essence. Even though he had the lower hand, he could stabilise his situation.

"First gen ancestor, good luck!"

"Lord First gen, we are cheering for you!"

"Ancestor, you are our only hope..."

The battle between two Rank five attracted everyone's attention. Fang Yuan however, retracted his gaze and looked at Bai Ning Bing.

This situation was like two tigers competing, while he Fang Yuan was a rabbit. Both the Lord Sky Crane and First gen Gu Yue were crafty old foxes. To wait for the two to injure each other and benefit Fang Yuan, such a chance was slim.

No one was stupid, they would not let the battle adrenaline get to their head.

Moreover, this blood barrier could only protect them for a while. Once the time is up, everyone inside including him would face the slaughter of Lord Sky Crane and First gen Gu Yue.

He had already rebirthed once, thus the Spring Autumn Cicada had fallen into a weak state again, unable to be used.

Right now, he could only try to get as strong as possible, exerting the greatest effort to fight for a chance to survive.

Fang Yuan already had a plan. But in this plan, there was a person who played a crucial role. That person is Bai Ning Bing.

The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's self detonation would greatly affect the battlefield. Especially when the two Rank fives were fighting outside of the barrier.

But how was he going to convince Bai Ning Bing?

Fang Yuan looked at Bai Ning Bing, and Bai Ning Bing sensed it, turning back to look at Fang Yuan.

Among the people, they stared at each other.

Fang Yuan in his black robe, with black hair and eyes, revealed a devilish smile as his lips curled.

"I have a way to resolve the ten extreme aptitudes, and allow you to return to life." He said.

Bai Ning Bing's body shuddered, he obviously wanted to live. "What method?"

However, Fang Yuan's words changed. "But this method does not have much chance of success, it is highly probable to fail."

Yet this made Bai Ning Bing even more convinced.

Next Fang Yuan said his third sentence, "But I think even if we fail, it will allow your final moments to be as spectacular as ever."

Bai Ning Bing's was moved.

Fang Yuan used three sentences and targeted his heart's innermost desires, convincing him!

He was also smart, and after thinking, he asked directly, "Then what do I need to do?"

Fang Yuan's smile disappeared. At the same time, the Problem Nipped in the Bud Gu turned into a puddle of blood water.

Blood Skull Gu and Yin Yang Rotation Gu's seal vanished and were about to fly away, but Fang Yuan grabbed onto them.

He used the Spring Autumn Cicada's aura. These three Gu were merely Rank four, they were immediately tamed. Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence and refined them, turning them into his!

"What? Fuck!" Outside the blood barrier, First gen Gu Yue's head hurt as he lost the connection with the Blood Skull Gu and Yin Yang Rotation Gu.

He was beyond shocked, losing his bearing and rushing towards the blood barrier!

"How can this be? How could you refine my three Gu worms so quickly!" First gen Gu Yue cried out sadly, attacking the blood barrier like a crazed man.

Fang Yuan stole food from a tiger's mouth. By taking the Blood Skull Gu and Yin Yang Rotation Gu, it was a fatal blow to the First gen.

Everyone was shocked, taking a step back. First gen Gu yue was like a fierce beast trapped in despair, his eyes starting to burn with fire.

But quickly, Lord Sky Crane's attack came.

"I want you to die, I want you to die!" First gen Gu Yue went frantic, attacking without defending, exerting all his anger on Lord Sky Crane.

Lord Sky Crane was taken aback as he received some damaging blows.

The two fought it out again, as the battle slowly reached its climax.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, saying to Bai Ning Bing: "Come, kill them all with me!"

Before he finished, he acted. As the razors on the Chainsaw Golden Centipede moved, he slashed a Gu Master nearby into half!

Blood Skull Gu!

Soon after, Fang Yuan activated the Blood Skull Gu, absorbing the blood.

Chapter 198: Ruthless in murdering people, cruelty exercised to profit from disaster

"Fang Yuan, what are you doing?"

"Quickly stop, the enemy is before us, how can we fight among ourselves?"

"Stop now, otherwise... urgh!"

Everyone was shocked. Fang Yuan was ruthless, killing another clansmen.

"I am only killing Gu Yue clan people, outsiders fuck off! Otherwise I'll kill you as well!" Fang Yuan screamed.

Everyone was stunned, retreating steps away, not expecting Fang Yuan to be so insane.

"Fang Yuan has lost it!"

"He's lost his logic, attack together!"

"Indeed, if this goes on, even before the first ancestor defeats the enemy, we'd have been slaughtered by Fang Yuan already...."

It was like Fang Yuan stabbed a beehive, causing everyone to stir, but no one dared to attack; most could only shout and encourage others to fight.

"Hahaha, interesting!" Bai Ning Bing laughed loudly, suddenly attacking and killing someone beside him.

"Lord Bai Ning Bing, you!" The dying person was a Bai clansmen.

"Oh no, Lord Bai Ning Bing lost it too!" Everyone shouted.

Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated, looking at Bai Ning Bing, not expecting him to change so drastically.

Bai Ning Bing laughed maniacally, "Since you can kill your own clansmen, I can't lose to you. Sigh, since too many deaths have occurred, Bai clan's future is ruined already, we can no longer be a village. The clan leader I'm indebted to is dead too, I might as well kill them now, and enjoy the fun."

"Hehehe, that's great," Fang Yuan laughed heartily, his body moving quickly, starting his slaughter.

Since these clansmen were going to die anyway, they might as well die at Fang Yuan's hands, contributing to his aptitude growth instead of First gen Gu Yue.

These people in the blood barrier, how could they be a match for Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing together? Especially when Bai Ning Bing who was nearing death, was much stronger and killed even more people than Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan took the last hit and extracted their blood.

After killing a hundred people, the Blood Skull Gu reached its limit, and the crystal skull started to turn blood red.

Fang Yuan laughed heartily, activating the Blood Skull Gu, raising it over his head.

The teeth opened, shooting out a fragrant blood stream, drenching Fang Yuan from head to toe.

Fang Yuan enjoyed the discomfort and breathed in deeply, living in the moment.

His black robe and hair together with his bloodbathed body, made him look like a demon straight out of hell. The surrounding people upon seeing him, were all scared and cried out in fear.

"My aptitude really increased!" Fang Yuan's aptitude was only 44% C grade originally, but after the Man-beast Life Burial Gu, it dropped to 43%. Right now, standing under the blood stream as it gushed into his aperture, his aptitude rose by 10%, going to 53%.

"Indeed a great treasure, no wonder First gen Gu Yue treated it like his life!" Fang Yuan opened his eyes, nodding in satisfaction, starting another round of slaughter.

The two caused much bloodshed within the blood barrier.

This was a large slaughterhouse.

"Fang Yuan, you mad and crazy monster!" Gu Yue Mo Yan rushed up.

Fang Yuan dodged her attack and raised his Chainsaw Golden Centipede before throwing it down.

The young girl was split in half.

"Fang Yuan, let us go please, we're your uncle and aunt!" Gu Yue Dong Tu and his wife kneeled down and begged.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly, his left hand waving, and a blood colored moonblade shot out, beheading the two.

Blood Skull Gu absorbed the Gu Yue clansmen' blood, turning into a thick blood stream, pouring into Fang Yuan.

"What a pleasure..." Fang Yuan closed his eyes, breathing in deeply, only to feel a warm feeling travelling through his body and causing his mind to become sharper, like he had been reborn.

Aptitude rose again, becoming 63%!

A Gu Master's aptitude, 40-59% was C grade, 60-79% was B grade, and 80% and above was A grade.

Fang Yuan had officially left C grade and become a B grade talent!

"But, my cultivation dropped..." Fang Yuan opened his eyes, staring intently.

Fang Yuan's aptitude rose to B grade, but his cultivation dropped from Rank three to Rank two.

Strange!

First gen Gu Yue evidently retained his cultivation level as his aptitude rose, so why was it that when it came to Fang Yuan, such a thing happened?

"This problem should be due to the Stone Aperture Gu!" Fang Yuan sighed in his heart.

Fang Yuan had used the Stone Aperture Gu to squeeze out all his potential, causing his cultivation to rise to Rank three peak stage. But this Blood Skull Gu injected the quality blood stream into him, raising the aperture's potential and raising his aptitude.

Undeniably, these two Gu clashed in nature.

But Blood Skull Gu was Rank four, while Stone Aperture Gu was Rank three. The Blood Skull Gu ruled over the Stone Aperture Gu, causing Fang Yuan's aperture to turn from stone back to light. However, the cultivation increase that the stone aperture brought was also disappearing, and even reducing his cultivation in the process.

This change was something Fang Yuan did not expect in such a short time.

But Bai Ning Bing was getting stronger, he killed everywhere he went. Thus, Fang Yuan was able to keep his strength and stop attacking, only collecting the bloodline.

First gen Gu Yue who was outside the blood barrier, saw the people getting slaughtered and flew into a rage, screaming but to no avail.

He spread his bloodline, waiting for hundreds of years. It was all for this moment, killing his descendants to raise his aptitude. After planning for so long, in the end, someone else benefited from it.

"This lad, so young yet so ruthless, even more demonic than his ancestor!" Lord Sky Crane seeing this, was slightly shocked too.

The slaughter continued, until six hours later.

Fang Yuan's cultivation dropped to Rank one initial stage, but his aperture returned to being a light wall, able to recover primeval essence on his own.

He was bathed in blood over ten times, and towards the last few times, the effect weakened. The first few raised his aptitude by 10%, but the percentage continued to drop with each try.

But his aptitude had increased from the C grade 43% to over 90%.

90%, A grade aptitude!

A grade aptitude!!

"Five hundred years of my previous life, I only manage to raise my aptitude from C to B about 200 years later through pure luck. To think that this time, I can benefit from a disaster and rise to A grade." Fang Yuan clenched his fist, secretly excited.

Bai Ning Bing stopped his killing, walking over, "Next, what do we do?"

In the blood barrier, only the two of them were left. The others, whether it was Gu Master or mortal, were all killed.

Outside the blood barrier, no one was spared from the aftermath of the two Rank five experts' battle.

In the entire area, there was only the two inside the barrier, and the two outside.

Fang Yuan looked outside, saying casually, "Next, we wait for First gen Gu Yue to run into defeat, and the Blood Curtain Skyflower to vanish."

"And then?" Bai Ning Bing pursued.

"Then?" Fang Yuan turned around and looked at Bai Ning Bing, then he smiled, "Then you can go and die."

Bai Ning Bing was stunned.

"Oh? What do you mean?" Immediately, his eyes squinted into a line as his blue irises had a dangerous killing intent.

"The Northern Dark Ice Soul physique's self detonation is extremely strong. Even though your cultivation is weak, and the chances are not high, it should be able to hurt Rank five experts. After detonating, are you able to control the direction of the snow and frost?" Fang Yuan laughed.

"How would I know?" Bai Ning Bing's lips twitched. "I've never self detonated before!"

"I know you can!" Fang Yuan laughed heartily, patting his chest. Unknowingly, the image of Bai Ning Bing self-detonating previously appeared in his mind.

And that line—"Live for me, and witness the brilliance of this world!"

"I will stay by your side. After you detonate, and when the time is ripe, I will save your life and cause you to resurrect," Fang Yuan continued.

"What if you can't?"

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed plainly, "Then you need to bet. When you detonate, I will be by your side. If you suspect my sincerity, you can send the ice storm to kill me. You must've noticed already. That's right, my cultivation is already Rank one initial stage. By then, I will have no way to survive."

"But if you believe me, then I could be lying too. Eventually I will not resurrect you, because I have no way to do so. Thus, you need to gamble—whatever choice you make, not just what you are thinking, but also what you are considering in the moment before you die."

Bai Ning Bing was solemn.

Fang Yuan's words was telling him to gamble away. But actually, wasn't Fang Yuan betting too? He was using his own life as the wager, fully dependant on Bai Ning Bing's thoughts.

"Hehe. So exciting. So very exciting! Then I shall bet on it, haha!" A moment later, Bai Ning Bing raised his head, laughing loudly.

Fang Yuan did not care about him, but concentrated on the battle outside the blood barrier.

As expected, First gen Gu Yue had the lower hand, suppressed by Lord Sky Crane.

Although he replenished his primeval essence, he could not replenish it, so under a sustained battle, how could he compete with Lord Sky Crane?

Moreover, Lord Sky Crane was clear of his methods, and he would not allow First gen Gu Yue to take back any advantage.

"I AM SO FUCKING FURIOUS!" A moment later, First gen Gu Yue cried out, "Little thief, you destroyed my thousand year plan, I will spare you today. Someday, I will kill the hell out of you to appease my anger!"

Throwing this angry statement, First gen Gu Yue flapped his wings and escaped the battlefield, flying towards the skies.

"Don't think of leaving!" Lord Sky Crane quickly turned into a flash of light, chasing relentlessly.

Without their intense battle, this battlefield became quiet instantly.

This was originally the best time to leave, but the blood veil aurora became a huge obstacle.

Four hours later, the blood barrier was thinning, and was about to vanish.

But at this time, a white light flew over, turning into the Lord Sky Crane.

His body was full of injuries. A wound stretched from his left shoulder to his waist, so deep that his bones could be seen, overflowing with purple poisonous red blood. But his face was extremely uplifted, showing the happiness of getting his long awaited revenge.

His right hand held a skull, a blood covered face, it was First gen Gu Yue!

"He actually managed to kill First gen Gu Yue?" Bai Ning Bing showed astonishment.

Fang Yuan laughed instead, "It seems this old fellow hates First gen Gu Yue to the core. Hehe, to kill the First gen, he definitely paid a huge price.

While they were speaking, the blood barrier vanished, and there were no longer any obstacles between the two.

"Little thief, quickly hand over the two Gu worms. I am still in a good mood now, I might spare your lives. Otherwise, when the blood barrier vanishes, you will all die without a resting place!" Lord Sky Crane flew into the sky, looking down and laughing loudly.

Fang Yuan and Bai Ning Bing looked at each other before laughing lightly, not speaking.

"Lord Sky Crane flew into a rage. "Good lad, refusing a toast only to drink a forfeit, you deserve to get killed!"

Before he finished his words, he turned into a white light and assaulted.

Bai Ning Bing laughed grandly, taking a huge step in front, "I was waiting for you!"

Saying so, his body lost all color, turning into an ice statue.

Cold winds blew, and as winds turned into a hurricane, frost and ice covered the sky and the infinite ice river appeared.

"This is!" Lord Sky Crane did not expect it in the least that such a development would occur, causing him to be unprepared against Bai Ning Bing's attack, and was sealed into the ice.

Chapter 199: Walking towards their own destiny

BOOM! BOOM!

The ice glacier shook intensely as Lord Sky Crane carried out his attacks; he was about to break out of the ice layer in just a few seconds.

"We can't let this old geezer break free!" Fang Yuan shouted.

Bai Ning Bing couldn't speak anymore; after Fang Yuan's shout, he resolutely self-exploded one of his arm, turning it into vast amounts of frost wind. The wind swept through everything, the glacier spread and the ice layer rapidly thickened by a hundred feet.

Lord Sky Crane roared within the ice and started attacking in a frenzy.

Bai Ning Bing exploded his other arm. More ice condensed and the glacier repeatedly pressed down on Lord Sky Crane, suppressing him every time he tried to breakthrough.

Under Bai Ning Bing's meticulous control, the ice moved like an army, firmly entrapping Lord Sky Crane. Lord Sky Crane may be a Rank five Gu Master, but after killing Gu Yue first head, he was thoroughly spent. He attacked again and again, but couldn't break out in the end.

"It is actually Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique! But if you want to kill me with just this, you can keep on dreaming!" He suddenly realized and immediately activated Life-retaining Jade Burial Gu.

Green jade light came into being and covered his body. Then the rays of light turned from virtual to material, changing into a transparent jade coffin with Lord Sky Crane inside it.

This jade coffin was abnormally hard; even after trying multiple times, Bai Ning Bing was not able to put even a scratch on it. In the end, he could only add more ice layers around the jade coffin, forming an ice peak that was hundreds of feets high.

Fang Yuan had watched all this from the sidelines.

"Worthy of being a ten extreme physique!" He was impressed even though this was his second time seeing it.

Fang Yuan was standing right beside Bai Ning Bing. Right now, Bai Ning Bing had destroyed his two arms and was turning into an ice sculpture. Even his appearance was becoming indistinct as the ice slowly covered him.

Both his appearance and his consciousness were slowly dissipating. Once his consciousness fades, he would be completely dead.

As the ice layer started to spread towards himself, Fang Yuan was clear on what he had to do: It is impossible to escape by myself; I will be sealed and frozen to death by the glacier sooner or later!

"It's time." Immediately, he took out a pair of Gu worms from his aperture.

One black Gu and one white Gu were revolving around each other in an orbit, forming a light sphere of Taiji diagram.

This was the Yin Yang Rotation Gu.

"Go." Fang Yuan willed it; the black Gu immediately flew out and merged into Bai Ning Bing's ice sculpture.

Fang Yuan may just be a Rank one right now, but his aperture still contained large amounts of Rank three snow silver primeval essence which he almost used up in activating this Gu.

In the instance when the black Gu went into the ice sculpture, black light burst out everywhere; yin qi gathered from all around and formed into an energy vortex in the air. A completely new life force came into being within the ice sculpture, and started growing vigorously.

The dazzling black light dissipated; the ice sculpture cracked and broke into pieces, which then flew scattered to the surroundings.

A white gown, silver hair, intact arms, picturesque appearance with lovely blush on the cheeks; Bai Ning Bing broke free of the ice and came out!

The blizzard came to a sudden stop and the cold air also completely dispersed. The ice layer stopped a few inches from Fang Yuan, he had lived through this near death experience!

"I am really alive!" Bai Ning Bing was shocked. He looked at his pretty jade-like hands and then felt his whole body; his disbelief changed to ecstasy.

"Hahaha." Fang Yuan laughed brightly, "I used the Yin Gu of Yin Yang Rotation Gu on you, this Gu can change yang to yin and give you a complete transformation. It is a Rank four healing Gu and has the effect of bringing the dead to life. It has a weak point though, and that is—the Gu Master's aptitude will be lowered by 10% once it is used."

Bai Ning Bing possessed the ten extreme physique which was a 100% aptitude. Now, his aptitude was lowered by 10%, and was equal to Fang Yuan's 90% aptitude.

This news, to others, might have been grievious, but to Bai Ning Bing, it was joyous news.

"This feels great. My aptitude has been lowered, I no longer have the Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique. Haha, what does it matter if I only have 90%?" Bai Ning Bing started laughing loudly.

Fang Yuan, however, shook his head. "It is very difficult to change the ten extreme physiques. Although this method lowered your aptitude, as you cultivate in the future, your aptitude will also recover until the day it turns into Northern Dark Ice Soul Physique again. When that day comes, you will need to use this Yang Gu—it will turn you around again and lower your aptitude by 10%."

Upon saying this, Fang Yuan put back the Yang Gu into his aperture in front of Bai Ning Bing's dead-straight gaze.

"Yin Yang Rotation Gu all come in pairs; you have already used that Yin Gu, so only the Yang Gu on me will have any effect on you. Don't even think of stealing it, I have already refined this Yang Gu; I can easily order it to self-destroy with just a thought," Fang Yuan explained.

He only had Rank one cultivation now, but Bai Ning Bing was still a Rank three Gu Master; naturally he needed some ways to stop Bai Ning Bing from taking actions against him.

"I see, Fang Yuan, you really planned it all!" Bai Ning Bing heaved a long sigh, "What do you want from me for that Yang Gu?"

"Hahaha..." Fang Yuan laughed for a good while then turned serious, "Qing Mao Mountain has already turned into a desolate ice mountain. The three great clans along with countless living beings have all been frozen and will die within three to five days. Such a scene will definitely attract the attention and investigation of many forces. Moreover, that old man isn't dead and has sealed himself within the jade coffin, waiting to breakout. We can't stay in Qing Mao Mountain anymore, we need to leave."

"But look at me, I only have Rank one cultivation now; I can't even take out my Gu worms, much less leave by myself. Hence, I need to rely on your strength. This world is so big, so wondrous, and Qing Mao Mountain is only a very small part of it. Follow me as I roam this land, and witness the wonders of the world!"

"It was like this! You really planned out everything. Humph!" Bai Ning Bing grinded his teeth. He was really happy but there was also some resignation now. However, as it turns out, Fang Yuan's proposal moved him. "I can agree to you but I need to make one thing clear."

"What?" Fang Yuan asked.

"It is not me who is following you, but you who is following me as I roam the lands!" Bai Ning Bing's red lips slightly raised with an arrogant smile.

"Hahahaha." Fang Yuan laughed heartily.

"Then, where are we going next? What do you have in mind?" Bai Ning Bing asked.

"Bai Gu mountain." Fang Yuan answered in between his laughters.

"What's so funny?" Bai Ning Bing was truly puzzled.

Fang Yuan laughed until his tears flowed, "You still haven't discovered anything wrong?"

"What is there that's wrong?" Bai Ning Bing raised his dark eyebrows; suddenly, his face turned extremely wonderful.

Surprise, fear, puzzled, panic, shock, anger... all these expressions intertwined in her face.

She looked at her round and full chest, and cried out with a loud voice, "I, how did I become a woman?!"

The voice resounded throughout the Qing Mao mountain, shaking the snow.

"Of course it would be like that! Yin Yang Rotation Gu—Yin Gu is used in male body, to turn yang into yin, and become a woman; likewise, Yang Gu is used in female body, to turn yin to yang, and become a man. Yin Yang Rotation, rotating yin and yang... what do you think it means?" Fang Yuan spoke like it was what it should be.

"I, I... what the fuck!" Bai Ning Bing looked at Fang Yuan with a furious gaze and cursed. With this, she must now get hold of that sole Yang Gu.

"Brother Bai, calm yourself, being able to live is the greatest fortune," Fang Yuan consoled her."Fortune my ass, how about you try being a woman?!" Bai Ning Bing's furious growl resounded within the snow covered mountain and glaciers.

Two days later.

The sun hung high in the sky; the ice was melting down and a stream of clear water flowed through the ice mountain.

Crackle....

The silence of the surroundings was broken by the cracking of ice; a jade light burst out from within the ice and hovered in the air, turning into a jade coffin.

The jade coffin exploded, and Lord Sky Crane gave a long cry upon regaining his freedom and seeing the daylight again.

This Life-retaining Jade Burial Gu was a Rank five Gu and was very mysterious. As long as the Gu Master had one breath of life in him, it could suspend his life and delay the injuries. Not only this, but the jade coffin it formed was extremely strong and could even be considered a defensive weapon.

"Goddamn thief!" He cursed with a pained voice. Right now, he was both furious and impatient.

Even after killing his lifetime enemy, the First gen Gu Yue, he couldn't get the true blood sea inheritance; how was he going to answer his teacher when he returned?

According to his memories, the ice layer where Fang Yuan was supposed to be was already cut open.

"If only he didn't get far!" He patrolled the surroundings hoping for a lucky break.

He used his recon Gu and discovered many life forces hanging on to their lives in the depths of the ice layers.

Living beings were tenacious and this tenacity could often bring about miracles. It had only been two days since this glacier covered these life forms, which was not enough to lead to their complete deaths.

"Found him! To think he was actually hiding here, hmph, the most dangerous area is the safest place, right? This guy is really crafty!" Lord Sky Crane's whole body jolted and became indescribably happy upon this discovery.

He rushed into the ice layer and soon fished out an ice chunk.

Within the ice chunk, Fang Zheng's whole body was covered with a layer of moonlight from the Moon Raiment Gu. He was already at the edge of death's door.

Lord Sky Crane could swear he would never forget Fang Yuan's appearance in this life.

However, he was a Rank five expert and after closely looking at Fang Zheng, he was immediately disappointed. "This person isn't him, only their appearances are similar. Sigh..."

He heaved a deep sigh before suddenly becoming stupefied.

"Wait a second, their appearances are so similar which means they are extremely likely to be twins! If so, then he is closely related to that little thief!" Lord Sky Crane's dim old eyes suddenly burst out with a sharp gaze.

With a close relative on him, he could refine the Kinship Blood worm!

It was because of this Rank five Kinship Blood worm that he was able to locate the First gen Gu Yue among this vast world and its diverse life forms.

"I haven't completely failed teacher's assignment. There is still some hope. This kid is my only hope. I must save him!"

Fang Zheng slowly opened his exhausted and heavy eyes.

"Where is this?" His eyes were still hazy and he could only see a blurry figure before him. At the same time, his whole body felt weak, along with an intense headache.

The last thing he recalled was the three clans competition, where Ironbeak flying cranes covered the sky and everyone around him had fled.

He had activated the Moon Raiment Gu and resisted against the flying cranes' attacks. As the battle continued, a flying crane broke through his barrier and pecked fiercely at his forehead.

He had immediately lost consciousness, tumbling down the cliff.

"You are the elder standing on the crane?!" As he became clear on the identity of the person before him, Fang Zheng struggled to get up in shock, but fell down again before he could completely stand up.

"Kid, you are still thinking of escaping in front of me, Lord Sky Crane?" Lord Sky Crane sneered.

He sized up Fang Zheng once and said, "You could say that I am even your lifesaver. If not for me, you would have already frozen to death. I advise you to not move around randomly, don't blame me if you fall down."

Fang Zheng looked beside him and immediately got a great shock.

There were clouds moving all around him, and he was standing on the back of an enormous crane as it flew in the sky.

"You, who the hell are you? Where are you taking me to?" Fang Zheng cried out in alarm.

"I am Lord Sky Crane, and we are heading to the Middle Continent."

"Middle Continent?!" Fang Zheng shouted in shock.